ScrubLifeChoseMe: y000
Quev1337: good evening
ScrubLifeChoseMe: good morning george
revolutionist123: stream PogChamp
lucas9o: hi hello
samwilliamson7: What’s good George!! Keep up the good work
Ahxs: yooo
Quev1337: shit its morning in NA :D
andrewfashion: you're my hero
madmanb11: hello
MrTriharder: hello groot, your twitchslam has inspired me to code it in c for college project :) @georgehotz
tqk_twitch: yay! i actually was hoping it gets ported to python 3
ScrubLifeChoseMe: no cofeee?
bosapiutsa: TriHard 7
TheLifeIsYours: hey man, loved your speech at SXSW
sam_dill: morning sir
ScrubLifeChoseMe: LUL
ScrubLifeChoseMe: LMFAO
dragan2271: hi
andrewfashion: I will help you get famous
Cape_clear: ...
andrewfashion: on IG
aknaveg13: Elon is looking for you bro🚀
ScrubLifeChoseMe: LMAOOO
dragan2271: bro im learning python right now
Quev1337: stream has been lagging for like a year
480i: George will you shill my tea company
tybutnowyoudie: tybutnowyoudie subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months! I love you <3 please stream regularly
Quev1337: whats wrong with your connection :D
Ahxs: @georgehotz put a bounty on that 1 million follower goal
samwilliamson7: What’s your thoughts on psychedelics ?
revolutionist123: TriHard 7
Cape_clear: can you play Bach ?
serhejenos: serhejenos subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 5 months!
Runner76: @georgehotz i’m a brain surgeon and a tech havy. My big dream is to make a big company that will connect brain technology like with cyberwares / augmentation. Do you think this is a waste of time or a real deal?
Cape_clear: can you play Bach A.I?
xyz: hi dad. how you doing?
480i: Skeet skeet
2knucklechamp: @runner76 ? Neuralink?
nanodanger7: nanodanger7 subscribed at Tier 1. They've subscribed for 10 months, currently on a 10 month streak! 10 months yoo
notelex: more programming yay
2knucklechamp: @runner76 elon musk is already doing that lol
jamesmaloney: High tech solution
geracao_7a1: the cam is lagging
ultrakaos_: is your haircut the next big trend in the influencer world?
MrTriharder: hey George, your twitch slam video has inspired me to code my own slam in c for college today :) I'm gonna copy your math :) @georgehotz
serhejenos: hi, glad to see you again
TheLifeIsYours: geracao_7a1 the whole stream is lagging
Runner76: Neuralink is amateur
Prest0n1337: If you stream more i'll give you my prime sub on the 2nd :)
Anarhi99: i missed it? god damn it
toolegit2quit_: hahah; day in the life of George: Hi, guys so while I was off stream I wrote... *Google cuts power to his house*
bosapiutsa: back
toolegit2quit_: back
roland________: Paying respects 😞
serhejenos: calm down everyone
revolutionist123: saved
tybutnowyoudie: back
Prest0n1337: PogChamp back
myaocat: back
bosapiutsa: saved
data_day_life: we back
semiproplayerstv: we good
samwilliamson7: Back
myaocat: yo its geohot and those who dont know im getting sue by sony. rap rap voice
foxubu: Hello George! Nice to see you’re getting active again here :D
pau1riddle: Why rewrite Qira in Python when Rust is superior choice
litesam: I caught you live
Ahxs: We’re good 4Head
ImAventus: Just watched an ad
ScrubLifeChoseMe: monkaS IP
loktarcek: Cut your hair man
erichtp: erichtp subscribed with Twitch Prime.
myaocat: can you just run python2to3 tool?
tybutnowyoudie: did you go hiking?
nanodanger7: hey @georgehotz just created a PR kinda fixing copying text from the UI
erichtp: erichtp subscribed with Twitch Prime. They've subscribed for 2 months, currently on a 2 month streak!
geracao_7a1: soo lag bro :'(
Scheback: is it only me or he has so many drops ?
sh4kesbeer: where is dude?
ajtourville: How's your Instagram push going?
myaocat: stream is lit
called_pb: fine for me
kriptonsteps: hi there
Ahxs: How was sxsw? @georgehotz
pau1riddle: I heard Docker is not cool anymore
myaocat: why not?
Blizzie: just download more ram
480i: Yay pagefile
andrewfashion: i aspire to be genius like this guy
yeah_haey: hello
pau1riddle: Kubernetes won, and it doesn't need Docker, so Docker the company is going down
knilecrack: wsup mann
MrTriharder: anyone knows what happens to his Comma AI startup?
Prest0n1337: @georgehotz Have you checked out Ghidra the tool released by the NSA for RE
samwilliamson7: Get influencers to shout your page out!! That would help with your instagram
sam_dill: i feel like im watching league of legends but I didnt know what a mouse was b4 i started watching
sam_dill: pls help
semiproplayerstv: show things
ultrakaos_: can someone please explain to a nontechnical person like me what he is doing? thx in advance
nonamehack: Yes it does
nonamehack: Sources tab
andrewfashion: he's being a badass @ultrakaos_
SonOfSatan: port error most likely
JackKrozzer: Where is he?
nonamehack: The.n insert breakpoint
myaocat: @ultrakaos_ porting a program he wrote to a new version
nonamehack: Insert a breakpoint in the sources tabb
hAhamza: georgehotz yo wtf what happened to geohot?
pau1riddle: Dropping frames
MrTriharder: Can someone inform my why his Instagram says ex startup CEO? what happened to comma ai
ultrakaos_: thx guys
SonOfSatan: lag spikes
serhejenos: @ultrakaos_ tryies to exploit a vulnerability in fontconfig. qira is progam he wrote awile ago for debagging
twiggy_io: Hes just not the CEO anymore
c19946: George would you manually enable ads???
Prest0n1337: Mac is garbage
myaocat: mac is shit
ScrubLifeChoseMe: shoulda got a mac
toolegit2quit_: we should fund a streaming macbook
ScrubLifeChoseMe: oh wait
tybutnowyoudie: you are rich as fuck, buy a new one
Incurs0: LUL
myaocat: install gentoo
Noxique: Yeah its dropping frames BibleThump
c9bd: shouldnt use a mac
yeah_haey: why did you sell your old mac are you running out of money ?
480i: Is it the quad core model
bosapiutsa: mac omegalul
knilecrack: trashhhh
Swayys_: Its not bad
Ziv0: lower bitrate maybe?
Prest0n1337: Mac is hipster garbage
MrTriharder: @twiggy_io so what he do now?
Blizzie: yikes 8gb ram
SonOfSatan: 8gb ram of
Lothsun: 8gb of ram. Lmao.
nonamehack: 16gb minimum
SonOfSatan: oof
knilecrack: quad core my ass
erichtp: scammed lol
knilecrack: 2 cores and 2 threads
called_pb: can easily stream on 8
Lothsun: Should go 32
Scheback: buymoreram.com
SlimEconomy: you have good money, just get a new one lel
Prest0n1337: Maybe you can take it to a Genius bar and ask them whats wrong LUL
arisnotle: hi
serhejenos: enven?
yeah_haey: why did u sell ur old mac u going b roke ???
nonamehack: I honestly don’t have lagging issues
serhejenos: envenc?
knilecrack: stream at 720p
480i: Can obs use quicksync
Prest0n1337: get a $2k repair bill
revolutionist123: my smart sleepers are faster LUL
c19946: sooo much lag
myaocat: you can buy a computer to record the mac somehow
bosapiutsa: LUL
Swayys_: Use NVEC
jperez94: PogChamp
nonamehack: Oh wait now I do
knilecrack: you don't have any hardware
knilecrack: (y)
480i: Also the 13 mbp doesn’t have a dgpu
samwilliamson7: Hit the drop down arrow
nightknight0000: lag is probably from your external 5k monitor
knilecrack: man, I have an idea. Just write your own
twiggy_io: doubtful
Lothsun: Why didn’t you max out the MacBook Pro?
Prest0n1337: Intel graphics thats your problem right there KKona
myaocat: my laptop is faster and the price is cheaper than macbook
nyanpaspas: MrDestructoid CoolStoryBob
semiproplayerstv: fix it first
butterscotchftw: butterscotchftw subscribed at Tier 1.
nonamehack: Hardware encoding in real-time isn’t well. CPU is better. GTX cards don’t do real time good.
twiggy_io: videotoolbox
twiggy_io: Yeah my guy.
PhillipWei: HeyGuys
ferrari_pizza: hi geohot, did u manage to execute code?
yeah_haey: when are you going to learnsome algebraic topology
twiggy_io: Nah it comes with OS X
smileyisdeath: yoo brother whats up
Blizzie: i skipped the touch bar but did take the 16gb ram upgrade
Lothsun: Ram makes a huge difference when streaming
sh4kesbeer: wait you have 8 gig?? I have 8 im my 7 year old macbook air and it aint funny
Prest0n1337: yep
myaocat: no lag now
myaocat: oh nvm
SonOfSatan: quick buy the 16gb version with next day delivery
Anarhi99: u jinxed it man... myaocat
Prest0n1337: lagging
SlimEconomy: just programm your own obs lmao
revolutionist123: Built a pc and stream it PogChamp
twiggy_io: You have to stop streaming before you can change the streaming options.
semiproplayerstv: call me when ready
yeah_haey: dude just go buy a new macbook and come back in 1 hour
c19946: just try to not move your head a lot it s fix the lags
480i: 32gb MacBook Pro
knilecrack: fuck them
myaocat: i want 4k
knilecrack: go 720p
Anarhi99: yeah fuck 'em
toolegit2quit_: I think 13inch doesn't have hardware
Scheback: stop the stream and then tune the settings bro
toolegit2quit_: it's a software type of computer
smileyisdeath: check obs estimator bro
myaocat: can you stream from tesla hardware?
twiggy_io: You have to stop the stream to change streaming settings.
semiproplayerstv: uninstall
SonOfSatan: just stop using chrome bro it eats your ram
PhillipWei: programming genius tries to figure out how to stream on steam Kappa
nightknight0000: CPU throttling due to temp??? elevate it for airflow or some SHIT bro
knilecrack: give ti a shot we will be here
twiggy_io: It will show up after.
Anarhi99: turn the stream off, see if the settings show up @georgehotz
yeah_haey: why arent you on linux if you are going to ssh anyway ????
480i: But when you streamed before you didn’t have an external
m0etaz: you streaming on youtube ?!
nanodanger7: go 720 fuck youtube
Morning29: should use the fastest encoder preset
r00tgp: hi
alienware997: We just want to see qira running on new mac os and in Python 3. fuck the Resolution!
nonamehack: Nvidia only
nonamehack: I think?
IamBurno: I think at the top you need to change output mode to Advanced then you get the hardware encoders - you might not be able to change while streaming
Prest0n1337: your macbook is dying
PhillipWei: i don't think this is anything to do with gpu
Prest0n1337: your using it wrong
480i: He’s on a 5k monitor and streaming
m0etaz: i can't seet a live stream on your youtube channel
m0etaz: see*
Ahxs: Intel HD graphics is by far the worst
myaocat: not really
yeah_haey: live stream on youtube
c19946: you should respect this 200 people time who whatching your stream
Lothsun: I hope apple does something great with the pros this year. The hardware is really falling behind.
nonamehack: I thought it’s only compatible with nVidia cards
nightknight0000: intel power gadget
smileyisdeath: @c19946 hahhahaha x
Prest0n1337: ResidentSleeper
andreas_bylund: @c19946 He does? lol..
myaocat: i able to play fortnite on intel graphics
480i: At least the intel gpu is reliable
yeah_haey: just use the comma ai supercomputer to encode
nightknight0000: https://software.intel.com/en-us/articles/intel-power-gadget-20
mciancia: use intel power gadget
Prest0n1337: Apparently you didn't get the news that Mac's blow
Ahxs: Fortnite isn’t really that graphics intesive especially if you bump down the settings lmao
nightknight0000: macs fan control is better
andreas_bylund: yea
tybutnowyoudie: yes
nonamehack: It’s fi e
knilecrack: fuck yeah
nonamehack: Fine
deep5: yes
serhejenos: ges
Ahxs: Yes
gerntt: yes
knilecrack: be the 1st dude
yeah_haey: please use linux
Prest0n1337: Get a real machine
data_day_life: I mean it would probably be fastest
nonamehack: I use it all the time
480i: Yeah
pau1riddle: yes
myaocat: you can build a self driving car but can't fix an issue
knilecrack: only
Prest0n1337: It's lagging
Quev1337: there is no way its throttling its maybe your internet
seanxedge: thats bad LOL
480i: Desktop time
ables91: it looks fine
ferrari_pizza: ferrari_pizza subscribed at Tier 1.
serhejenos: its lagging
Ziv0: LUL
tybutnowyoudie: only 20% LUL
Anarhi99: oops nvm dropped again
idutcher: Open activity monitor
jgab19: it's lagging
smileyisdeath: its actually lagging bro seriously
some_kind_of_god_of_wide: LUL
nonamehack: It use SMCfan all the time
swagettiyolonaise69: only 20
sudqijawabreh: this is not gaming guys
Prest0n1337: it's like watching a bunch of quicktime videos
480i: No video cuts out for me
Ahxs: ONLY 20%
Quev1337: lag again]
shutchie: eGPU
sh4kesbeer: bit annoyng tho
Morning29: it definitely uses less cpu
nightknight0000: lag is acceptable
mciancia: change resolution from 5k to 2.5k and check
Morning29: the preset is a huge factor
hartator1: its fine on mine!
W1lkins: next frame please :)
myaocat: @mciancia make sense
tybutnowyoudie: nice power point presentation
Lothsun: @480i then something is up with your internet.
idutcher: Lower it since, you have high cpu power low GPU
revolutionist123: 100%
Scheback: george bro,we are watching like at 20fps
hartator1: it does freeze time to time actually
fortnest: just lower the resolution
480i: @lothsun Don’t think so. Video is just frozen. Audio is fine.
knilecrack: bro we gonna bitch about stream whole time :)
kevczy: I’m back
myaocat: only the camera is freezing
pau1riddle: It's 2019 and we still can't have smooth video over the internet
yeah_haey: acd ghidra support to qira with auomated analysis
knilecrack: @pau1riddle no
480i: I’ll just watch the archive on YouTube later.
W1lkins: best security? LuL
knilecrack: it's not same experience
kevczy: Are we working on qira again?
nanodanger7: @georgehotz just created PR fixing copying from the UI
tybutnowyoudie: the video on youtube will also contain the dropped frame...
twiggy_io: Refresh with network up
buraknml: Any idea what's his favorite programming language?
kevczy: Yea
SlayerDarth: Hey George and chat.
kevczy: Python obviously
SlayerDarth: How's it going?
SlayerDarth: Hey kevczy and buraknml
deep5: just build a hackintosh
kevczy: @slayerdarth good thanks
smileyisdeath: lmfao?
Anarhi99: a race condition?
Anarhi99: no whites allowed
SlayerDarth: When two operations attempt to run at the same time
SlayerDarth: But they must run in sequence.
knilecrack: rofl
Lothsun: Mac Pro?
Prest0n1337: race condition are when two things happen at once and then the result is which ever completes first
knilecrack:
c9bd: lmao
jacopo_l98: Hi
SlayerDarth: Any idea how many viewers are here?
Anarhi99: 212
twiggy_io: Race condition is when two thing try to read/write data.
SlayerDarth: I am not watching on Twitch.
SlayerDarth: Oh wow.
twiggy_io: At the same time.
grizvok: @georgehotz I just watched the SXSW talk...pretty fucking nutty man. Some good arguments.
Yellow_turd: what ide do you use
kevczy: @yellow_turd terminal lol
Quev1337: sublime text
grizvok: he's using vim mostly right
serhejenos: @yellow_turd vim
Quev1337: mostly ye
kevczy: It’s a joke guyss
SlayerDarth: NeoVim
SlayerDarth: I believe.
myaocat: god the drops
c9bd: so what does this application do?
semiproplayerstv: delete windows
Prest0n1337: he's porting an existing app to python3
kevczy: He tried vs last stream lol
twiggy_io: https://github.com/geohot/qira
kevczy: Which is qira!
grizvok: does one of the docker containers need to wait for a different one to be up?
myaocat: qira is a web debugger
Anarhi99: kevczy vscode?
buraknml: Can you port everything to Python? I doubt you can.
asazin118: never expected to see you here twiggy
Prest0n1337: Check out Ghidra @georgehotz
kevczy: It’s a “disassembler ”
pau1riddle: Twitch penalizes the stream becuse it's not popular enough
kevczy: It works smooth for me
Caene: Dude, you looked great with the beard. You should let that grow out again. Full homo. @georgehotz
ferrari_pizza: so geohot dropped hacking the fontcache...stuff
kanogger: kanogger subscribed at Tier 1.
kevczy: Every developers are full homo to George
Caene: jQuery DansGame
eduardoadf1: nice talk sxsw
Caene: LUL
kevczy: Are we getting some Mac Miller today?
Aerdeyne: cmonBruh
W1lkins: cmonBruh
theGeekPirate: DansGame
kanogger: thank you for streaming, first time I catch you live
aerotone: it doesnt print loading ui when u reload
kevczy: Mac Miller
legalweaponss: What's good family
tybutnowyoudie: LUL
Anarhi99: 4Head
ScrubLifeChoseMe: mLUL
eduardoadf1: me :)
PhosphoricAcid: me :D
Anarhi99: just rewrite it all again
Anarhi99: 4Head
ferrari_pizza: .. now taking care of qira..
dontusethiscode: Feel like 1m2019.com needs a shoutout @georgehotz
myaocat: Qira used in challenge on youtube stream https://youtu.be/411BiewfNrM?t=1292
estilen: I for one welcome our new python3 overlords
sh4kesbeer: why write in python 3 when 4 is around the corner?
lordFOE: did geohot really write this shit?
myaocat: @sh4kesbeer really?
aknaveg13: Did you create my simulation?
myaocat: ;_;
smileyisdeath: # // who the hell knows if this works? LMAOOOO
ferrari_pizza: ... he doesn t remember
myaocat: i barely know python 2
gankeomenores: what is he doing rn?
SSKarizma: then stop learning and move to 3
ables91: xD
zolllo: typescript masterrace
myaocat: @SSKarizma are you talking to me?
zgamer0123: george why the stream is lagging in some moments?
grizvok: callbacks are such shit lol
grizvok: promises are great
myaocat: maybe use ltrace or strace on your script
tybutnowyoudie: @zgamer0123 because his pc is bad
idutcher: call debugger() xd
twiggy_io: They compile to the same thing though.
ables91: yea promises for the win
pau1riddle: TypeScript is not the rise, jQuery is deprecated
lordFOE: !keyboard
myaocat: guys we need to fund a computer for geohot!
idutcher: i mean debugger;
grizvok: It's irrelevant if they compile to the same thing lol
snapcs1: LUL
shadilayyy: js in 2015 LUL
gouvernatorn: BCWarrior
JonThomasK: please dont go into modern JS its still crap
idutcher: @grizvok That's the same thing as saying C and C both compile to binary
zgamer0123: @tybutnowyoudie isn't it a mac? So it shouldn't have any problem
Prest0n1337: you assemble to binary bro
Prest0n1337: you compile to assembly
Anarhi99: wait, your todos dont end with questionmarks? monkaS
twiggy_io: Not always.
Anarhi99: only me? anyone else? no?
Prest0n1337: yes
tybutnowyoudie: @zgamer0123 it is a macbook with 8gb of ram
JonThomasK: if you load data its doing a javascript promise most likely (async request) and then running the UI dom load
nyanpaspas: CoolStoryBob
grizvok: He's not using promises in any of this
lordFOE: Anyone know what keyboard hes using?
civicbooks: your ui script call is last in index.html if that matters
JonThomasK: ill go check out qira
p7081: damn geohot nice. greetings from germany
PlayITBruiser: hello george
Aer0skull: As a student I'm lost with all this web oriented things, there is too many way to do something I want and can't find a proper way to do it
PlayITBruiser: are you ok today?
st47ik: @Aer0skull just pick one lol
lightofhel1: only me got stream lags?
st47ik: it's not lagging for me
myaocat: @lightofhel1 try reboot
grizvok: @Aer0skull it's programming. there are always multiple ways to do something
ferrari_pizza: someone told me, PHP is still on top of things
grizvok: LOL php
st47ik: someone
myaocat: wordpress uses php
st47ik: it's actually 80% of the web
twiggy_io: Yeah php is still used a lot.
sh4kesbeer: php top 1 machine learning lang
myaocat: saying php is bad it's same as saying c is bad and same as saying C is bad because they are based on the same thing
ferrari_pizza: anyone using elixir ?
JonThomasK: @grizvok he's using defferred.. they all have a promise. Exactly the .done call
c9bd: thats an awful argument lol
zolllo: PHP 7.0x isn't too bad
st47ik: PHP is old and established
Aer0skull: @grizvok sur, but in web, there is no reason to do that way than an other (reason like optimisation, performance, etc...)
twiggy_io: @Aer0skull https://developer.mozilla.org/en-US/
twiggy_io: They set a lot of good standards for the web.
ApexJnr: @georgehotz sorry if it's a daft question, im late, what are you up to?
the_sadanie: just tuning in. what is the project?
pspxdiso: Hey Mr. Balls
twiggy_io: Hes working on https://github.com/geohot/qira
st47ik: Porting Qira to Python 3 is the title mates
Aocuser: Now he is making Qira work at least
ApexJnr: i saw the title but i also see js
ApexJnr: so i was confused if it's the same thing
JonThomasK: we are porting all of qira into JS
JonThomasK: Kappa
Blizzie: Anyone know what keyboard and switches he uses ?
pau1riddle: I remember Terry Davis saying that it's bad enough that it gets clusterfucked on its own, and then there is CIA fucking it up on purpose. Maybe CIA corrupted QIRA
wisdom_tgo: wtf started follwing this channel several months ago and this is the first time seeing you live, coincidentally since i saw your presentation on the simulation hypothesis yesterday.
Aer0skull: @twiggy_io thx, yeah I somethimes check that, but I think I'm lost because I have so much to learn about web
0xEbi: I'm still using your CFW 2.55 man. My PS3 is stronger than ever.
pau1riddle: Was QIRA some kind of Noogler project? Like what noobs at Google do to get accepted?
ZABITAMEMURU: hello georgie <3
ferrari_pizza: @geo @all bye, have a nice weekend
knilecrack: bye
wisdom_tgo: Im convinced he doesnt have chat open.
pau1riddle: @ferrari_pizza don't die
mohammdomar: hello next elon musk
pspxdiso: Damn this guy is busting balls out here
tomastakk: not using IDE DansGame
grizvok: @Aer0skull not sure what you mean by "sur, but in web, there is no reason to do that way than an other (reason like optimisation, performance, etc...)"
wisdom_tgo: This guy is going to be at the forefront of autonomous transportation in a couple of years.
W1lkins: LUL
wisdom_tgo: lmfao
ZABITAMEMURU: remember us george, never forget me <3
wisdom_tgo: LUL
ZABITAMEMURU: i want to visit you <3
ZABITAMEMURU: i want to meet you <3
b4qazan: hey george, what you doin
wisdom_tgo: George Hotz are youi Jewish?
740ii: im too hungover for python and geohot right now
snapcs1: yall are weird
HIGHFIcs: is it just me or is he dropping frames?
ZABITAMEMURU: i think he is muslim
wisdom_tgo: @snapcs1 yes you are correct
Santiago_LHC: Frames are overrated
wisdom_tgo: wtf muslim=
davidsit_site: @snapcs1. tis the internet
0xEbi: which keyboard and switch is that?
wisdom_tgo: Im not talking about the religion
tybutnowyoudie: @HIGHFIcs it's him
wisdom_tgo: i mean his ethnicity
wisdom_tgo: zabita
snapcs1: @davidsit_site remember be <3 never forget me <3
ZABITAMEMURU: oo lol :D sorry @wisdom_tgo
Manasoiu: i see him dropping frames
bosapiutsa: pog
hintz3y: PogChamp
1garo: pog
Santiago_LHC: DA BOY FIXED IT
nyanpaspas: CoolStoryBob CoolStoryBob CoolStoryBob
Aer0skull: @grizvok for example, what he said before, what should we use between yarn or npm
Manasoiu: BibleThump <3
gmrfreak: Do you suggest learning vim well or is that just what you are used to?
wisdom_tgo: Is GeoHot of jewish ethnicity?
myaocat: damn i didnt see how he fixed it
PhillipWei: @gmrfreak i think you should learn vim then decide for yourself
hintz3y: cheer100 ez number one cheer spot
ZABITAMEMURU: @wisdom_tgo i think GeoHot is Turk
PhillipWei: its worth learning but not necessarily using
civicbooks: you can use defer in the script tag in index.hml
740ii: yes learn vim @gmrfreak
PhillipWei: the philosophical idea of how to be keyboard efficient is indispensible
wisdom_tgo: ENTP
neca420: just know that once you learn vim there is no going back
knilecrack: what are you doing man, except dropping frames?
Santiago_LHC: You shouldn't do anything that works for others, just because it works for others. Code however the fuck you want.
gmrfreak: I have done some but the time you have to put in to be faster than a visual IDE takes time
Keyeh: hello mr. Geo
pau1riddle: It's kind of cute that on Mac you can get this behavior with windows like you're using tiling WM
MacoNighto: Only if you don’t do emacs
davidsit_site: except for when you use any program that doesn't support Vim keybindings
Prest0n1337: I read up on your Qira project pretty interesting should be useful
Prest0n1337: Is this a IDA plug-in?
kanogger: no lol
fission1110: if something doesnt support vim key bindings I write it in vim and copy paste lol
Kultiviert: just use angular george hotyyy
740ii: its a standalone debugger
grizvok: @Aer0skull i mean those are small things...simply package managers. it really isn't going to make a difference if in your personal project to learn you use yarn or npm. yarn is still faster but npm has audit now which is pretty nice
fission1110: almost everything supports vim bindings though
Aer0skull: @grizvok or what framework shoud we use to make a website, as a beginneri have no clues
pau1riddle: If you think about it, it's really conceptually better than lldb and gdb.
Prest0n1337: oh okay it has integration
Santiago_LHC: A framework for a website? Depends what kind of website
dontusethiscode: Remember when this stream was full of roasting
dontusethiscode: good times
snapcs1: i wan to make website tell me if u are jewish
wisdom_tgo: ARE YOU JEWISH GEROGE HOTZ!!!
acheesedanish00: fucking hell
bruce_oath: Jebaited
myaocat: i dont think he is jewish
erichtp: lmfao wtf
Santiago_LHC: What's wrong with people
ZABITAMEMURU: @wisdom_tgo NO, he is TURK
myaocat: why are you keep saying that
Keyeh: noobs WutFace
snapcs1: LUL
wisdom_tgo: How the fuck do you know that?
grizvok: @Aer0skull I think the idea of isomorphic js is really powerful nowadays
ZABITAMEMURU: I know it I feel it
wisdom_tgo: ITs because you are turkish
wisdom_tgo: He's last name is germanic
wisdom_tgo: could be jewish
ZABITAMEMURU: hahah lol
Santiago_LHC: Does it matter at all "what" he is?
Manasoiu: wish i can code fast like my mans
ultrakaos_: guys, what are now the big thinks in silicon valley, i guess in the last few years it was software for b2b companys, like construction software
myaocat: he is american
ZABITAMEMURU: @wisdom_tgo where are u from
Manasoiu: i have to use mouse and click lmao
wisdom_tgo: American is an aextremely vague definiton of ethnicity.
740ii: he is anglo saxon
Santiago_LHC: @ultrakaos_ I'm hearing good things about MySpace
aPosterior: he is quite likely a male
JonThomasK: qira is F'ing awesome @georgehotz
civicbooks: your dockerfile pulls direct from github
onu4r: yo
onu4r: what do u think about zoom s-1?
ZABITAMEMURU: I think, geo is viking, he looks like them
wisdom_tgo: are you JEWISH GEROGE
grizvok: @Aer0skull imo create-react-app with a node backend is a great way to go
andrex_andrex: hi all
JonThomasK: I'll fix it for you
ultrakaos_: @Santiago_LHC really, i will take a look on this, thx
austin_1_2: NotLikeThis NotLikeThis
civicbooks: more fun to watch you fix it
wisdom_tgo: Curly brown hair, smart and the hotz surname. Jewish Jewish Jewish
onu4r: what do u think about zoom s-1?
myaocat: @wisdom_tgo are you german?
Manasoiu: is it better to keep on learning app dev natively for android with java or should i stop and learn javascript and develop apps with react
wisdom_tgo: Nope
snapcs1: is this gonna help us break out of the simulation
Manasoiu: im at a standstill on what i wanna do
myaocat: or do you have something with jewish?
grizvok: @JonThomasK whats the best way to resize it...multi-stage builds?
ZABITAMEMURU: @onu4r kardaş ne diyom
dontusethiscode: Does he still even work at COMMA.AI
Keyeh: comma.ai just use his name for advertisement
davidsit_site: @dontusethiscode lurkers and name changes admit nothing, this is a good upstanding community (not some hacker hangout). Have you written anything worth using recently? ..I jest, I watched your last presentation. nice
myaocat: youtube will copyright the video?
Santiago_LHC: Did he say Pokemon?
MrBankster: lil pump is fire type?
ZABITAMEMURU: he go for poop
JonThomasK: thats one way.. the biggest one is to reduce the amount of commands needed
Aer0skull: @grizvok k, thx for the tips
serhejenos: LULW
onu4r: @zabitamemuru Zoom IPO yapacak çok hoş bir s-1 yayınladılar ne düşünüyorsun diye soruyorum
kanogger: PogChamp
TheSelfMadeHero1: PepePls
snapcs1: YUH TriHard
kanogger: TriHard
740ii: cmon man
kanogger: YUH UH YUH UH
wisdom_tgo: He is taking an incredibly big poo right now.
aPosterior: i think i hear it
Keyeh: HYPERBRUH
kanogger: YUH YUH YUH YUH TriHard
Prest0n1337: TriHard should've played gator skin
ZABITAMEMURU: @onu4r adam yorumları okumuyor hiç, sağında monitör bakmıyo
iamaflex: my diamond sink
wisdom_tgo: ARE YOU JEWISH GEROGE HOTZ?
kanogger: i say gator gator
myaocat: Keepo
dontusethiscode: @davidsit_site wtf
740ii: put on some old man rap music wtf is this
onu4r: @zabitamemuru aynen
tybutnowyoudie: DansGame
bosapiutsa: TriHatd 7
JonThomasK: He has 6 run commands so the size will duplicate each time @grizvok
kanogger: ayyyy TriHard
yeah_haey: this is literally the worst thing ive ever head in my life even 69 is better tha nths
ZABITAMEMURU: @onu4r s-1 ne babuş
0xEbi: BabyRage BabyRage
Prest0n1337: mind you
hintz3y: @georgehotz you should lower your bitrate a little bit, you're dropping frames
grizvok: @JonThomasK interesting. im newer to docker...probably like 2 months or so i'
Manasoiu: yeah
JonThomasK: qira docker size: 1.31GB LUL
Manasoiu: he keeps lagging for me
grizvok: I've been using it*
Santiago_LHC: Influencer
data_day_life: Bro you should setup a treatstream and chat will send you food that you pre-selected
onu4r: yo have you seen zoom s-1?
snapcs1: george what inspired you to talk about the simulation? just for fun?
480i: Nice segue
Prest0n1337: I will make a insta just for you
Justlegend34: hey
onu4r: @snapcs1 to get some attention ofc
Santiago_LHC: lol that URL
kanogger: just buy some Kappa
saulgd: is george on the spectrum?
myaocat: 2019?
onu4r: @snapcs1 you know he likes attention
Prest0n1337: You look skinny cause your hair got bigger
snapcs1: @onu4r LUL
iamaflex: modafinil shaming
wisdom_tgo: Check your DM Geroge.
PlayITBruiser: make a fat program
JonThomasK: Pog
Aocuser: 1m2019 . com
MrBankster: lol
Justlegend34: LUL
Santiago_LHC: Order a salad
serhejenos: lol
revolutionist123: LUL
740ii: just dont eat shit food man
nsielicki: have you tried 2to3? how much of this really needs extensive effort?
480i: Drink soylent
Santiago_LHC: Ramen is not good at all
A_footlong_sub: just dont be poor man
davidsit_site: carbs vs protein....
snapcs1: especially if you put... half an egg in it thats good protein
foxubu: Loool
Manasoiu: SALAD
1garo: chicken
tybutnowyoudie: mc donalds very healthy
740ii: lmao
nsielicki: jie-row
wisdom_tgo: Geroge, ARE YOU JEWISH JESUS CHRIST I'M DESPERATE AND NEED THIS QUESTION ANSWERED
Santiago_LHC: If it looks good, it's not good for you
Prest0n1337: don't eat a gyroscope
nsielicki: it's gee row
decap__: lyndGrill lyndGrill lyndGrill
480i: Steak
myaocat: @wisdom_tgo russian/germans are smarter than jewish
snapcs1: gyro is delicious
MrBankster: cbrahGirls cbrahGirls cbrahGirls
myaocat: if that is your question
serhejenos: salad
erichtp: chicken
740ii: thai or vietnamese food
myaocat: only kosher
onu4r: eat some kebab man
wisdom_tgo: @myaocat Ashkenazi jews have a higher average IQ
grizvok: falafel
nsielicki: come for the live programming, stay for the nuances of choosing lunch
wisdom_tgo: @georgehotz Are you Jewish?
davidsit_site: bacon?
ultrakaos_: some germans here?
saulgd: @wisdom_tgo he's called hotz WHAT DO YOU THINK
Prest0n1337: go on a bacon only diet
Santiago_LHC: I guess it could be wrose
PlayITBruiser: 88
A_footlong_sub: Get some tahini sauce
Justlegend34: O_o
kanogger: @ultrakaos_ Ja
snapcs1: i followed but you never post
yeah_haey: you never post SHIT and don't even make stories
wisdom_tgo: @saulgd HOTZ
wisdom_tgo: @saulgd I HAVE TO HEAR HIM SAY "YES" OR "NO"
myaocat: @wisdom_tgo also some have crohn disease https://www.healthline.com/health/crohns-disease/jewish-ancestry
Santiago_LHC: the mobile Wikipedia link on your insta profile, rubs me wrong.
snapcs1: Kreygasm
decap__: lyndGrill lyndBeer
Manasoiu: anyone have an opinion on what i should do, should i keep learning how to make native apps with java for android, or should i learn javascript and make shit with react
JonThomasK: That's ez. I can reduce the file size to like nothing too if you want
ZABITAMEMURU: @onu4r sen niye izliyon bu adamı babuş
saulgd: @myaocat LUL that trivia
nsielicki: just use 2to3
d0neall: lagging for anyone else or is my connection shit 🤔
wisdom_tgo: His name is PewDiePie
myaocat: @Manasoiu people use now kotlin
slashHOTS: jQuery? Am I in 2005?
LightZumo: Hi dude ^^
jesseslco: same lagging
onu4r: @zabitamemuru qira bunun yazdığı hoş bi tool onu py3'e portluyor o yüzden
kanogger: @d0neall it's his webcam only for me
foxubu: With this hair cut you look so much younger :D
saulgd: @georgehotz how tall are you?
JonThomasK: we got that asyncio queue Pog
pau1riddle: https://www.2to3.com/#!
d0neall: @kanogger Right true
saulgd: READ TFKN CHAT
Manasoiu: @myaocat ik, but the course im taking on udemy uses java
whynoxx: this is live?
austin_1_2: PogChamp
ZABITAMEMURU: @onu4r meslek yazılım mı
whynoxx: is this8
wisdom_tgo: George hotz, i like you but i need you to answer ARE YOU JEWIH?
onu4r: @zabitamemuru yup
myaocat: @Manasoiu go with what you are interesting imho
snapcs1: LUL
whynoxx: HAHAHAH
1garo: HAHAHA
hintz3y: @wisdom_tgo why does it matter what the fuck
ZABITAMEMURU: @onu4r nerde çalışıyon
LightZumo: does anyone know which laptop he's using?
austin_1_2: PogChamp
snapcs1: i have more followers than you LUL
saulgd: im unfollowing on insta if NO VIEWER INTERACTION LUL
Manasoiu: @myaocat im just at a standstill, i wanna be a software enginner later on but dont know what path i should take
wisdom_tgo: @hintz3y It's a personal Hypothesis i want it to be confirmed or denied
Santiago_LHC: We are getting so close to 1 million followers
gluecks: georgehotz what are you coding today?
wisdom_tgo: George hotz are you jewish?
nightknight0000: @wisdom_tgo pls go
Santiago_LHC: @gluecks check the title
myaocat: @Manasoiu as i said. but ima failure so my advise will be shit
wisdom_tgo: @nightknight0000 Die
onu4r: @gluecks He's portin qira to Py
hintz3y: where the mods @
grizvok: @Manasoiu how long have you been programming? it's advisable imo to stick with one language for a while when you start out.
acheesedanish00: kick wisdom_tgo please for being an asshat?
myaocat: ^ this
Santiago_LHC: I concur
nightknight0000: @acheesedanish00 yes
saulgd: i think the anti-semtism in this chat should be addressed LUL
Santiago_LHC: asshat is the worst kind of hacker
dontusethiscode: @georgehotz check out my speed challenge attempt
snapcs1: he never said its a bad thing
gluecks: onu4r alright, thx
hintz3y: There's no anti-semetism, it's just mad weird
dontusethiscode: https://github.com/Quantzz/commaai-speed-challenge
nsielicki: can you please explain why 2to3 isn't capable of doing this automatically?
myaocat: ^ this
nsielicki: my understanding is that it's very complete
saulgd: ask him what he thinks of palestine omegalul
nsielicki: and that's why they've aggressively deprecated python2
Bence657: cause its written in javascript lol
Manasoiu: @grizvok about 2 years, i started with python for a class i took freshmen year in high and I've been learning java to prepare for next year when i take ap comp sci, but i really just want to make stuff as side projects and to build a portfolio for when i apply to jobs later on
myaocat: palestine is bs. israel is offical country
hintz3y: He's gonna glance at chat and see us talking about he conflict in the middle east
Bitcoin__: Hey
hintz3y: Wack
myaocat: guys there is no palestine on eurovision you will see israel
grizvok: god damn it MOM
kingkontraa: I don't have a clue what's going on, but I enjoy seeing this
snapcs1: hi mom HeyGuys
Manasoiu: @grizvok ive also worked with a team at my school making a game in unity and competing against other schools
MajesticMack: Tell mom we said hey
decap__: HI MOM
LordMunta: hi mom
740ii: hopefully mom doesnt read the chat
serhejenos: hi mom
gluecks: hi mom
foxubu: Html does not exist in python 3
brotas_: hi mom
ZABITAMEMURU: @onu4r bu qira ne işe yarar
saulgd: MILF ALERT
MajesticMack: cmonBruh
karelomab: HeyGuys mom
wisdom_tgo: His moms surname was orginially goldberg
Bitcoin__: Bitcoin__ subscribed at Tier 1.
grizvok: Goldberg?!?!
karelomab: Geomom
wisdom_tgo: George are you jewish?
snapcs1: LUL
Dsplits: use the virtual env
myaocat: django or nodejs or flask for backend?
onu4r: @zabitamemuru runtime analyzer
twiggy_io: Go backend.
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?
grizvok: I just started learning Go. I'm in love.
Santiago_LHC: Why are people so.... internet
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?!
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish???
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?34
acheesedanish00: GTFO
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?142
onu4r: @myaocat flask is super lightweight
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?456
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?15
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?65768
twiggy_io: I love Go as well.
myaocat: BANNNNNNNNNNNN
nsielicki: @georgehotz why doesn't 2to3 autoport it?
wisdom_tgo: lmfao
onu4r: @myaocat which is sometimes super useful
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?52
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?15
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?643
snapcs1: lol
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?sr
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?we
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?q35
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?u32
ZABITAMEMURU: ban @wisdom_tgo
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?253
Manasoiu: ban
grizvok: @twiggy_io It's my second language after js...it is amazing honestly.
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?4
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?234
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?h
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?12
decap__: Autistic
brotas_: how to hack in html
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?tj
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?qw
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?123
wisdom_tgo: Geroge are you jewish?r
myaocat: @onu4r i looked that up and saying flask is for togo and not for big projects
ZABITAMEMURU: GER-OGE
saulgd: so much autism in this chat
Aer0skull: how to get ban
LordMunta: can someone ban this dbag pls
erichtp: mod me so i can ban this guy
RollingK: python3 -m venv venv
Santiago_LHC: I'm sorry that wisdom_tgo didn't get enough attention growing up
ZABITAMEMURU: /ban @wisdom_tgo
onu4r: @myaocat exactly
brotas_: yes he is jewish
d0neall: mod me so i can ban this guy
gdhameeja: @georgehotz What theme do you use for vim?
davidsit_site: @wisdom_tgo Warning before ban. Flooding chat. You will be able to keep posting but no one else will see your comments
myaocat: so nodejs or django?
Cape_clear: does he have German ancestry?
brotas_: jewish html hacker
acheesedanish00: thank you
twiggy_io: @grizvok the concurrency model is what makes it great for me.
ZABITAMEMURU: @myaocat i love nodejs but i think you should have a look mvc core
gdhameeja: What theme is that for vim?
grizvok: @myaocat i mean do you know js or python better?
Cape_clear: Hotz seems like a German name. Are you sure its Jewish?
saulgd: george is a scientologist guys, he has addressed this in the past. but he doesnt like to talk about it ok
Santiago_LHC: SIGH
Manasoiu: anyone have any thoughts on fullstack dev?
myaocat: @grizvok i dont know js and i learned python 2 a whileago. i dont mind what to learn but just wonder if there is a better or preference
gdhameeja: What theme is that?
gdhameeja: for vim?
myaocat: @ZABITAMEMURU no microsoft technology please
myaocat: im using linux
snapcs1: no such thing as fullstack anymore theres too much shit
Santiago_LHC: @Manasoiu Yeah, it's a bullshit invented by employers who only want to hire and underpay a single guy
monst3rcow: @cape_clear im from Germany and hotz defenetly doesn't sound like a German name.
thasetreksw: what's your opinion on cardano @georgehotz
ZABITAMEMURU: @myaocat mvc core can run on linux too
grizvok: @myaocat depends on use case. node will reign supreme for applications where you expect some long-running continuous connection
bosapiutsa: ubuntu omegalul
snapcs1: @Santiago_LHC TRUE LUL
saulgd: @monst3rcow OZIL doesnt sound like a german name either LUL
onu4r: @saulgd OZIL is turkish
KrypticNation: The typing noise Kreygasm
monst3rcow: @saulgd cause he migrated kappa
Santiago_LHC: Typing ASMR
OFFICER_KKONA: @georgehotz what tab management system are u using for iterm?
saulgd: iirc he has a german passport :thinking:
grizvok: @myaocat however you cant forget the power of an isomorphic app starting out imo.
Manasoiu: @Santiago_LHC damn, sounds like hell and i shouldn't get into that
gdhameeja: quality here is so much better than youtube
thasetreksw: hey lads is it lagging only for me
saulgd: mechanical keyboard WHEN
gdhameeja: What theme is that for vim?
KrypticNation: The video quality usually depreciates when you record from twitch
myaocat: @grizvok i dont know what and i want to create projects and also get experience to find a job
Santiago_LHC: @Manasoiu Don't. If you want to be a frontend dev, be a front end, if you want to be a designer, be a designer, if you want to do backend, do backend.
snapcs1: no lag here
Manasoiu: @myaocat same
grizvok: @myaocat then maybe try nodejs backend given that you are also writing the front-end in js
JSPeterson: save that beard bro
myaocat: @grizvok yea im not sure..
grizvok: @myaocat well its the fastest way to build a portfolio imo
Manasoiu: @Santiago_LHC im really just stuck at the moment, i want to either do that or be a software engineer but i realize how broad the field really is
gdhameeja: Guys, I've wanted to know the name of this theme ever since I started watching him
gdhameeja: What theme is that?
myaocat: is there difference between using db with nodejs vs python?
grizvok: Not really no. You probably use some node or python driver
myaocat: i want to work with database
brotas_: html hack mikenBrain
grizvok: for your db of choice
soreox: Good day
myaocat: ok thx
KrypticNation: learn mongo, that is growing quick
nsielicki: @myaocat this program spans several languages
myaocat: i will do more serach
Santiago_LHC: @Manasoiu Take the time to figure it out. It's a drag to get into a career only to figure out that you are not that into it while you are in the middle of it
JonThomasK: nodejs pisses me off
nsielicki: his database is in cpp for perf with bindings to python
snapcs1: just use typescript 4Head
myaocat: @KrypticNation mongo is nosql and dont think is good
kevczy: Lol
JSPeterson: do something fun For once like a Playstation app
nsielicki: frontend is obviously in the browser
grizvok: @myaocat yeah, imo go with a relational db first
thasetreksw: @snapcs1 i dont really get what typescript is. I know its based on js but what is it
kevczy: This is fun
grizvok: @thasetreksw maybe it adds types to javascript lol?
snapcs1: @thasetreksw js with types loool its actually good
Manasoiu: @Santiago_LHC sounds good, i have some time to learn and create projects, so many technologies are interesting but im just so clueless lol
saulgd: TAKE A MINUTE TO READ CHAT YOU AUTIST
KrypticNation: What is he coding right now?
nsielicki: you haven't addressed how 2to3 doesn't handle this
JSPeterson: writing what
thasetreksw: @grizvok chill boi i dont fck with js
JSPeterson: I always use PHP anyway
kozgn: @georgehotz is the current version of qira stable
myaocat: dont you think making a major version is bad? not because of making people learn new features but because of support old stuff
kevczy: Hmmm
thasetreksw: js is garbage so tyypescript is prob trash too
chamodac: terminal vs iTerm
gdhameeja: Does anyone know what theme he's using?
Manasoiu: what do software engineers mostly create at big companies? what types of technologies do they use to create software?
myaocat: if js is garbage install windows xp
kevczy: It’s sad that I work on js
myaocat: and see what is real garbage
myaocat: i hate people saying this X is bad or Y is garbage..
dontusethiscode: @gdhameeja its default theme for vim wdym
Bence657: That is kinde of ironic
Bence657: isnt it?
nsielicki: @gdhameeja looks like unthemed vim on xterm-256color
gdhameeja: wdym?
dontusethiscode: what do you mean
soreox: Bence657 yupp
snapcs1: if you cant figure that out then why you using vim
tybutnowyoudie: @myaocat comparing js with windows LUL
thasetreksw: xd
kevczy: Customized tmux on tmux.conf
Santiago_LHC: Agreed @myaocat Everything thinks their thing is the best. Fucking always.
nsielicki: @gdhameeja it's not themed, he's not using a vim theme, it's just the default iterm color palette
Manasoiu: linux B)
gdhameeja: I didn't know that. That's not the default theme for vim on ubuntu
Santiago_LHC: *Everyone
Thomasbrah: @georgehotz Finally i caught you streaming!
nsielicki: @gdhameeja change your gnome terminal colors
gdhameeja: So this is iterm?
kevczy: He’s using tmux if you noticed it
dontusethiscode: @gdhameeja yes, its probably you terminal theme that is different
gdhameeja: oooo
nightknight0000: That’s screen not remix
nightknight0000: Tmux*
el_pirulote: what is he programming?
grizvok: @thasetreksw yep, js is sooooooo baddddd
OFFICER_KKONA: is he using tmux?
lulascoca: sry but why use tmux?
smileyisdeath: multiple terminals
brotas_: @el_pirulote html
dontusethiscode: @gdhameeja default theme for Terminator looks kinda like his
kevczy: After finding out tmux exist I never used ides again
Thomasbrah: @georgehotz I have been watching all your streams on youtube while i code great background material! Love all the videos mate keep it up
Manasoiu: what is hotz's strongest language ?
el_pirulote: @brotas_ making html or using html?
nsielicki: after finding out emacs exist I never use terminal multiplexor again
2knucklechamp: @manasoiu english
brotas_: @el_pirulote hacking using html mikenBrain
thasetreksw: @Manasoiu python/ c i think
Number___Nine: c lol
Manasoiu: @2knucklechamp lmao
nathants_: use cffi instead of ctypes? easier
Manasoiu: c really?
Manasoiu: that language confuses me
Number___Nine: c 20
el_pirulote: @brotas_ shiiieeeeeeeet
nsielicki: ^^^^ CFFI for sure
Manasoiu: its interesting for sure
kevczy: It’s pretty easy
brotas_: ikr
erichtp: where is the uber eats at
farfdaddy: can we argue about the utility of learning python vs javascript please
kevczy: Lollllllll
nightknight0000: @farfdaddy Learn both?
knilecrack: yeah
knilecrack: not so hard
knilecrack: to be honest
farfdaddy: @nightknight0000 i can't read tho
gdhameeja: nsielicki But shells in emacs suck big time
gdhameeja: Not one functions properly
nsielicki: learn one programming language properly and, outside of ml and lisp variants, you know every language more or less
thasetreksw: @georgehotz are u still into crypto
kevczy: Even though people say that js is bad it’s one of languages that u need to know
gdhameeja: shell sucks, term doesn't let you use other commands, ansi-term doesnt give colors
Bence657: Not necessarily
Thomasbrah: @kevczy whats wrong with js ?
nsielicki: @gdhameeja nonsense, ansiterm is fine. they're slow if you cat a million lines, so don't do that.
Bence657: if you wont work with the web, you dont need to know js
grizvok: @kevczy exactly so saying dumb shit like I don't fuck with js is idiotic
robbsalm: I am studying computer science, I was wondering if you could give me a suggestion possible projects ( i know some python/java) and i am currently studying assembly for mips
kevczy: @thomasbrah I said “people” not me
Manasoiu: @robbsalm same
Thomasbrah: @kevczy fair enough but what are they saying is bad about js ?
gdhameeja: nsielicki ansi-term is the only one which comes close to being functional, and it doesnt provide colors
nsielicki: oh no colors!!!! grow up
kozgn: @georgehotz is the current version of qira stable?
Manasoiu: what are some projects i can build with java(as its my strongest language) thats worth putting on a portfolio?
thasetreksw: !uptime
Thomasbrah: Boop Kappa
FartKnockGomez: You can do it CoolStoryBob
gdhameeja: nsielicki Grow up? Talk to the kids using VScode then
hintz3y: @robbsalm write quicksort in MIPS, that's a fun one
gdhameeja: I use emacs with no autocomplete following george
kevczy: @georgehotz go to preferences and fix it pleasee
grizvok: @Thomasbrah there are some weird things about it. some of the equality stuff...some of the typeof stuff since everything is in an object...single threaded.
Thomasbrah: is he aware that his stream is dropping frames ?
erichtp: yes @Thomasbrah
robbsalm: I will do it #hintz3y
kevczy: It’s working great for me
Thomasbrah: @grizvok ok thanks for the answer
grizvok: @Thomasbrah But it has gotten so much better and I'd say is one of the languages improving the fastest
myaocat: next year he will port it to rust or something Kappa
FartKnockGomez: amiloSubs amiloAol amiloMail
ultrakaos_: hey guys, which sites would you recommend to somebody to learn basic web development and python?
kevczy: I bet that python will race up c and java in about 10years
davidsit_site: python.org
Manasoiu: @ultrakaos_ udemy
Thomasbrah: Got a pizza in the oven bois PogChamp
KAM0N: https://www.freecodecamp.org/
semiproplayerstv: meundies
Bence657: c and python have different use cases
Manasoiu: how big of a project is worth putting on a portfolio?
Thomasbrah: Anybody here would mind answering a simple Java question i have ?
Manasoiu: @Thomasbrah would do you got?
kevczy: You really shouldn’t need those freecodecamp and udemy u should really teach yourself much easier
davidsit_site: cpython is c and python....and @thomasbrah what's your skill level in java
nsielicki: @gdhameeja sane-term is the extension I use for sane ansi-term defaults
nsielicki: gives you colors among other things
nsielicki: but you don't need it anyway
myaocat: phantomjs is no longer maintained..
ultrakaos_: ok good thx
hintz3y: @robbsalm you could also write a pippin assembler/emulator. I did that in my first year of Computer Science and it's a neat project that helps you think about assembly but in a much simpler form
hintz3y: @robbsalm http://www.cs.gordon.edu/courses/cps111/Notes/Machine Language/mach1.htm here's the spec
kevczy: K I’m just gonna stop typing and and I’m just gonna concentrate on the stream
Thomasbrah: @Manasoiu If i want to create an array of objects in Java do i have to create a class that defines what this object contains and make get set methods ? or like javascript can i do something quicker like (  ); without typing the class up ?
Thomasbrah: Im very low skill level Java i would say
PhoenixLuffy: Is he using tmux??
bajcmartinez: isn't phantonjs dead by now?
robbsalm: thanks bro, i am half way through my first year! x) i will try to do it, but i was wondering what type of projects should i start for my git hub
myaocat: @bajcmartinez it is
myaocat: but seems he is just testing something
Thomasbrah: @bajcmartinez i heard google has something that is better now
Thomasbrah: chrome somethign
PhoenixLuffy: Selenium now has chrome drivers that are headless
bajcmartinez: @myaocat yeah the guy developing it gave up when google released puppeteer
myaocat: google chrome driver it's called
davidsit_site: @robbsalm projects that interest you
bajcmartinez: https://github.com/GoogleChrome/puppeteer
myaocat: google ruined everything
kevczy: Does he have his python chess sources in his github?
kevczy: That he worked on
ivanovcrimea: y
bajcmartinez: yeah, twitchchess or something
Santiago_LHC: Yup
Manasoiu: @Thomasbrah you can do the type of object with array(lets say ObjectClass[] a = new ObjectClass[5];
bajcmartinez: https://github.com/geohot/twitchchess/
bajcmartinez: @kevczy ^^
CaptainAshtar: :D brutal coding again in action love it
kevczy: Thanks babe no homo
Santiago_LHC: Twitchchess plays really poorly though.
Bioaim7: very basic Kappa
Manasoiu: @Thomasbrah just define the array with the object you want to devine it with
gdhameeja: How does he do this? Sit for 4 -10 hours in a row just coding?
kevczy: @santiago_lhc yea I’m gonna make it better
snapcs1: flow state
myaocat: curoisity i think
CaptainAshtar: what is the task @georgehotz
Lothsun: Did we figure out the frame drops? Sorry had to step away for a few
Santiago_LHC: @kevczy You may want to take a look at Stockfish while you are at it
bajcmartinez: @kevczy you would need to change quite a lot...
kevczy: @santiago_lhc thanks for the advice
myaocat: i think he is coding in a garage
alexanderqkc: "not to be total crap" nice
kevczy: @bajcmartinez yea I’m working on as a team
davidsit_site: @gdhameeja passion
CaptainAshtar: that's an attic not a garage
dkrisztan: any idea what vim theme he uses?
kevczy: I think he customized it
myaocat: thats not look like theme vim
dkrisztan: it has to be tho
Aer0skull: the stream is a bit lagy tho
Keyeh: he custumized tmux only, its on his github
myaocat: @dkrisztan you can google https://github.com/geohot/configuration/blob/master/.vimrc
kevczy: Yea it’s it’s prbly a vim cuztomized in the tmux
kevczy: Conf file
dkrisztan: oh thanks guys
gdhameeja: No its not
gdhameeja: I tried that
antfinn420: what is he trying to do right now?
gdhameeja: Doesnt change theme of vim
Thomasbrah: @Manasoiu how would i get the "name" of this object if the object structure is unkown ? like in javascript you would do something like object[name]
gdhameeja: on ubuntu
kevczy: @gdhameeja what do you mean? I customized my own
strminftr: read the goddamn title wtf^^
myaocat: @gdhameeja do you mean colors? its not really a theme
gdhameeja: kevczy Does it look like George's?
Bryanswagbeast: hi George! What are you doing? @georgehotz
kevczy: Not the exact same cuz I did my own
myaocat: everything looks good on mac
dkrisztan: yah
kevczy: Gotta make a tmux.conf file and restart all of the seesions
dkrisztan: feels bad to be a windows use xd
gdhameeja: How can I get my vim to look like George's? I dont care if its a theme or colors. I just want my vim to look like his. I am on ubuntu
dkrisztan: start to learn more about vimrc i guess
strminftr: 1
Santiago_LHC: SIGH
dkrisztan: like the basic commands and highlights
CaptainAshtar: nobody cares what you want
kevczy: Are you talking about the numbers? Or the colors
bajcmartinez: @gdhameeja what you mean? looks pretty standard, with a few settings in vimrc
myaocat: @gdhameeja http://voidcanvas.com/ubuntu-like-mac-terminal/
gdhameeja: bajcmartinez This is not the standard one on ubuntu
Bryanswagbeast: What is he doing?
dkrisztan: we should ask him for a full video on his tools and hardware too xd
bajcmartinez: he enabled syntax highlight and line numbers
Santiago_LHC: Learn to customize it then
bajcmartinez: syntax on set number
yamesboard: george, off topic: where would you start if you were to learn ai from scratch?
hintz3y: @robbsalm put literally anything that you've completed on your github, and use github a lot, having an active github is great
myaocat: @dkrisztan that would be a waste of time
bajcmartinez: probably those two commands ``` syntax on set number ```
snapcs1: yeah i dont get why you are using vim if you cant even figure out the colors
TiLeNpWneD: what keyboard do you have?
dkrisztan: @myaocat why ?
bajcmartinez: lol
dkrisztan: im curious
Santiago_LHC: @yamesboard Watch the Spielberg movie A.I.
dkrisztan: he has a steelseries keyboard
bajcmartinez: don't kill the guy, he wants to learn
hintz3y: @robbsalm if you're a student you get private repo's for free so you don't even have to make your projects public until you're happy with them
dkrisztan: not exactly sure witch one
myaocat: @dkrisztan there is many tools, vscode, jetbrains, vim, gvim, emacs, etc.
kevczy: Lol people asking the exact same questions every single stream
bajcmartinez: hahaha
TiLeNpWneD: ok, thanks
snapcs1: then he should stop wasting his time on useless stuff
myaocat: on his previous stream he showed his keyboard check his previous stream to see the keyboard
dkrisztan: @myaocat i know but i would be curious to see his full setup too u know a
gdhameeja: He has a lepold as far as I know
robbsalm: @hintz3y well i am ^^ first year in^^ cs in sapienza
dkrisztan: it's steelseries
snapcs1: this is like gamers obsessed with pro binds
dkrisztan: i know that it's not some rgb shit
snapcs1: its not gonna make you better if you still suck
dkrisztan: it's just simply a mecghanical keyboard
antfinn420: how do you set up breakpoints and step through code in the terminal like this?
kevczy: Ikr lol
gdhameeja: It's funny how people like me think we'll be as good as him with his theme and his keyboard and his hardware
CaptainAshtar: yes
bajcmartinez: lmao
Santiago_LHC: How can I have my hair done exactly like his? I figure it'll make me code just as good.
gdhameeja: As peter norvig says: Read code, write code
serhejenos: @hintz3y actually github make it possible for everypne make private repos.
bajcmartinez: they have orgasms with the keyboard sound lol
dkrisztan: true
hintz3y: @serhejenos they changed it? You used to have to pay for private
dkrisztan: he types so fluently
dkrisztan: if you can call that
serhejenos: @hintz3y yea couple of month ago
snapcs1: yeah they changed it so you have to pay for insights now
Santiago_LHC: fluidly
Tidusuper91: @antfinn420 In Python? You import `pdb`or `ipdb` and you put a trace in the line of code you want to break: `pdb.set_trace()`
serhejenos: @hintz3y thanks to Microsoft probably
gdhameeja: I went as far as buying a mech keyboard after I started watching hi,, it feels good to type on it. But it doesnt make you a better programmer
hintz3y: @serhejenos probably came with the microsoft takeover
hintz3y: @serhejenos yea
dkrisztan: mechanical keyboards are really good feeling
serhejenos: @hintz3y to not scare the userbase
gdhameeja: Yeah they are
dkrisztan: from laptop keyboards i like mcs
dkrisztan: macs*
gdhameeja: worth the money spent
dkrisztan: yeye
snapcs1: its to compete with gitlab
gdhameeja: I kinda hate mac's keyboards. Not enough feedback and keys are all mixed up
kevczy: People obsessed with hardwares never makes good softwares
antfinn420: @Tidusuper91 it seems to have nothing to do with the language and more about the fact that he's writing this all in this command prompt
Bryanswagbeast: yo guys what is he doing?
Pryetranka: OpieOP
kevczy: Terminal if you say so
Enm1ty: Wowee
dkrisztan: true but somehow the newer one that requires literally like 1 g of push makes me feel good
bajcmartinez: eating stream lol
Santiago_LHC: FOOD TIME
dorkmo: DoritosChip DoritosChip DoritosChip DoritosChip
Santiago_LHC: EATING ASMR
gdhameeja: kevczy Agreee
robbsalm: @hintz3y i have an idea but it seems way over my capabilities. Can i dm you?
CaptainAshtar: eating fast food crap agian
Tidusuper91: @gdhameeja Since I use a mac for my daily use I ended up switching keys on the Linux boxes I use trying to use the same mapping as possible...
myaocat: is he sell his macbook? i think i will be smart like him when i will touch it
hmnvdota: why python?
Noxique: DROPPED FRAMES NotLikeThis
dkrisztan: xddd
dorkmo: *starts paying attention for eating stream time*
davidsit_site: I can't imagine it's because they use it internally and see it as a valuable product # response to ref to github and Microsoft
dkrisztan: i dunno guys
K4tarina_God: what is he doing?
antfinn420: @Tidusuper91 but I guess I was just wondering maybe visually how hes able to step through each line and inspect the values of variables
bajcmartinez: what kind of crap food is it this time?
dkrisztan: I was thinking about switching to full time mac
yamesboard: george, off topic: where would you start if you were to learn ai from scratch?
dkrisztan: but not sure
Bence657: the mac key mapping is weird at first, but I started to like it
bajcmartinez: giro is not that bead... making progress bro! lol
antfinn420: skip the bread
myaocat: LOL
dorkmo: 1
Thomasbrah: @georgehotz I just want you to know that im so happy i finally caught you streaming!
deep5: atleast its thicc
snapcs1: wtf
gdhameeja: Tidusuper91 Yeah? I hate mac key bindings. Also the default emacs is kinda weird
hoffs: lmao
Pryetranka: winning
tybutnowyoudie: WTF
코케인: you just activated my google home
magggha: LUL
shadilayyy: OMEGALUL
dkrisztan: EMACS or VIM
myaocat: maybe tweet elon musk he will send you food
Santiago_LHC: ONE
dkrisztan: it's going down boizz
gdhameeja: emacs
MrBankster: nano
CaptainAshtar: lets continue ... love to see it
tybutnowyoudie: did you go hiking?
yamesboard: george, off topic: where would you start if you were to learn ai from scratch?
nightknight0000: there are tons of simple carbs in your pure leaf tea bro
gdhameeja: nano sucks bigtime dude
Tidusuper91: @gdhameeja I'm a vim guy... I have the same mapping everywhere. The problem is with all the Cmd Opt Ctrl stuff.
Santiago_LHC: No, it's not bread, it's beans
dorkmo: full screen eating plz
kevczy: @pykim77 Korean?
bajcmartinez: nano is vim for newbies lol
dkrisztan: notepad is the best so far
revolutionist123: LUL
bajcmartinez: notepad ???? wth! lol
MrBankster: i like the name Kappa
gdhameeja: Tidusuper91 Exactly, us emacs guys depend on Ctrl and Alt too much
bajcmartinez: that thing is still in light mode
myaocat: geo do you have alexa?
Tidusuper91: We want eating ASMR now!! LUL
gdhameeja: bajcmartinez That would be better than nano
dkrisztan: @bajcmartinez nah bruh u can customize it
Bombapil0t: yummi
kevczy: I messed up several projects with notepad lol
dorkmo: zluminum foil ASMR
hintz3y: @robbsalm sure
dkrisztan: yesterday downloaded it and was able to put monokai in it
serhejenos: boneapetite
snapcs1: one time i had an interview where they wanted me to write code in microsoft word lmao has anyone had that happen to them
gdhameeja: kevczy Messed up how?
bajcmartinez: I prefer sublime or atom over notepad
dkrisztan: holy
gdhameeja: snapcs1 Thats common
dorkmo: crinkly foil lightly next to mic plz
dkrisztan: fuck me with atom
Santiago_LHC: Notepad updates too fucking much, lol
bajcmartinez: plus I don't use windows... isn't that only windows thingy?
dkrisztan: it eats my ram so much
gdhameeja: bajcmartinez Sublime rocks
MrBankster: intellij
kevczy: @gdhameeja it corrupted the project and threw away all of the codes
Bryanswagbeast: Hey geroge what are you doin? Are you hacking today? @georgehotz
Thomasbrah: VSCode bois
gdhameeja: emacs sublime
snapcs1: @gdhameeja not really
dorkmo: it puts the gyro in the mouth
kevczy: Why do people think that the only thing he do is hacking
gdhameeja: MrBankster No offence, but fuck IDEs. I never feel the one in control while coding in them
snapcs1: how is writing code in microsoft word common lmfao
Santiago_LHC: @kevczy because fast typing, of course
snapcs1: you're nuts
gdhameeja: And so many pop ups
dkrisztan: i mean i like atom and all but it eats my ram and takes to much time to load in files etc.
kevczy: @santiago_lhc loll
dkrisztan: sublime fan myslef
DrRobotvinnik: whoa he's gone pro Twitch, has a strim icon and everything PogChamp
revolutionist123: What are u eating? @georgehotz
gdhameeja: snapcs1 They ask you to do that in interviews, its commonly discussed on reddit
bajcmartinez: @kevczy I'm sure he can also troubleshoot my office lol
kevczy: After finding out tmux now I can’t work on IDEs
MrBankster: @gdhameeja sounds like a personal problem
CaptainAshtar: Bon Apeti @georgehotz
Tidusuper91: IDEs are tools. We should try to not forget that and spend 80% of our time in tuning tools! :) [I confess, did it, plenty of times]
Thomasbrah: Y'all ever try coding in Microsoft Word 2013 ?
kevczy: @tidusuper91 great comment!
bajcmartinez: Word coding is the best!
Santiago_LHC: Is there any other way to code @Thomasbrah
Bryanswagbeast: hey guys why does he run his code by typing all of that? That isn't a IDE right?
gusfrehse: every day his hair gets longer
dkrisztan: it's vim
antfinn420: I'm just curious how to step through line by line with code in a command line
dkrisztan: or vi
snapcs1: @gdhameeja dm me threads? google pulls nothing
Santiago_LHC: It's not an IDE, it's a terminal
kevczy: @bryanswagbeast nope it’s terminal
Bryanswagbeast: oh ok thanks
CaptainAshtar: @Bryanswagbeast that's better than IDE
ShinyFux: @santiago_lhc VIM Terminal
Bryanswagbeast: I want a Mac now lol
kevczy: Indeed
bajcmartinez: Mac or Linux
Thomasbrah: i want to be good at vim but i just can't be f'ed to start learning
revolutionist123: i code on libre writer
bajcmartinez: stop using windows lol
kevczy: @bryanswagbeast you don’t need a mac
Bombapil0t: typespeed > 9000
ShinyFux: @bajcmartinez mac
Santiago_LHC: @ShinFux It's just the Mac terminal. He is using Vim on it
myaocat: mac is good for designers
ShinyFux: @santiago_lhc yes ik
myaocat: many tools there
kevczy: You can use putty or xshell or it’s own server
dkrisztan: @Thomasbrah i recommend to go through it's totorial located in it's folder, it's pretty interesting
Keyeh: mac is good overral
bajcmartinez: Mac is good for coding... I use a mac, anything with a decent terminal is good... hence no windows lol
dkrisztan: or u can learn vim by cutomizing it
gdhameeja: As long as I can use a terminal and emacs and a browser, any os works for me
myaocat: windows is good too
Keyeh: except for gaming but only that
gdhameeja: Ubuntu rocks
yeah_haey: what do you need the terminal for ?
ShinyFux: @bajcmartinez linux also good
bajcmartinez: windows is only for gaming lol
Thomasbrah: @dkrisztan i will check it out didnt even know it exsisted
0TestUser: is there a fixed stream schedule ?
davidsit_site: no
kevczy: He’s connected to ssh guys
bajcmartinez: @ShinyFux yeah, I have ubuntu on the other laptop, I used to have arch linux... but gave up after a system crash lol
yeah_haey: literally what are you doing with the terminal for on linux that you can't do on windows
gdhameeja: Windows mostly sucks for devs. Its hard to install stuff
Santiago_LHC: Stream schedule? Look at his eating habits. This man doesn't know the term schedule.
gdhameeja: Its hard to find stuff
yeah_haey: it's easier to install stuff on windows than linux on linux you have to compile shit yourself
ShinyFux: @bajcmartinez i have arch linux
gdhameeja: Its hard to control stuff
Bryanswagbeast: so he's using Vim and the Macs terminal but what about the highlighting syntax?
bajcmartinez: @ShinyFux cool! that's the good stuff
kevczy: Linux graphics got wayyy Better wdym
strminftr: @gdhameeja can you explain that? :D
gdhameeja: yeah_haey Nope. sudo apt-get install <insert package name>
Thomasbrah: @dkrisztan what is folder called ?
CaptainAshtar: why all of you are interested only in the colors ... ? is that matters at all?
bajcmartinez: @yeah_haey windows is so painful to install anything decent lol, not to mention terminal sucks.... and python is a nightmare
gdhameeja: strminftr Explain what?
ShinyFux: @bajcmartinez yes i think arch linux is the best linux for me
Bryanswagbeast: what's highlighting his syntax?
bajcmartinez: anyone using mac hates that it ships with python2 default? lol
Santiago_LHC: HOW CAN MY COLORS BE LIKE HIS COLORS. I WANT TO COMPUTER LIKE HE COMPUTERS
myaocat: @CaptainAshtar geohot is popular and i assume they are news to this stuff
frankie98_: mainly see devs using windows or mac.. linux to run servers etc. really just depends on what you're doing
strminftr: @gdhameeja I see no sense in your argumentation, although your thesis seems to be right :P
bajcmartinez: guys we are over syntax highliting on vi/vim lol
bajcmartinez: scroll up
ShinyFux: coding on rasberry best Kappa
bajcmartinez: hahaha @ShinyFux going hardcore lol
gdhameeja: Its hard to find stuff on windows coz all you can do s Ctrl F, on a terminal, you can be like grep -Rn --include="*.py" RandomShit . And you can control what you search and shit
nizero: sup George, I met the comma ai team in Phoenix, they were all very nice
Bryanswagbeast: I heard he mentioned in a video that he likes to use Flask as an open source and I also heard he likes to use Sublime to write code
bajcmartinez: windows has a crappy file system... period lol
bajcmartinez: c:wtf? lol
ShinyFux: @bajcmartinez yes pros coding on rasberry
myaocat: why this isnt in science & technology
ReDD_TV_: "basic" programming
felipeit999: Hi
Keyeh: he uses sublime to read code no?
Santiago_LHC: Yeah, to read only
bajcmartinez: @Keyeh vi/vim
antfinn420: wait is Trace a specific command here or something that he's defining in his code
gdhameeja: windows is good for noobs only, although I'd consider myself a noob as well
Impruner: vuoi aiuto?
Tidusuper91: Damn, still talking about tools? Guys why are you so obsessed by his tools? :)
gdhameeja: according to george's standards
ShinyFux: intellij best
bajcmartinez: lol
Tidusuper91: @Impruner Lol. Italiano? :)
bajcmartinez: Jetbreains rocks!
myaocat: next is i want geo food too
ShinyFux: @bajcmartinez yes
Impruner: @tidusuper91 certo
itsChoudhry: hey what keyboard does he use?
frankie98_: i wouldnt say windows is for noobs. everyone has their own preference
Tidusuper91: Impruner: grandissimo!
bajcmartinez: Pycharm all the way!
gdhameeja: Tidusuper91 Coz we think if we use his tools we'll be as smart as him, we copy him, me included, its wrong
myaocat: where do you buy food geohot
gdhameeja: ShinyFux No offence, IDEs suck
ccb2: What kind of keyboard does geohot use?
bajcmartinez: Run windows, start a VM with windows 7 and run Pycharm on top to code!
spectre1001: how do you get OBS to work with mac, i can never get it running properly on display capture. And rest of the modes don't good fps.
Impruner: hahahahah tu ci capisci qualcosa?
gdhameeja: ccb2 lepold 750R
ShinyFux: @gdhameeja nooo
myaocat: https://www.reddit.com/r/MechanicalKeyboards/comments/4t41vl/what_keyboard_is_geohot_using_in_this_video/
Tidusuper91: @gdhameeja: I know the feeling, perfectly legitimate. It's like wearing football jerseys :)
myaocat: lets stop this stupid question
bajcmartinez: ides are good for some things
Keyeh: @bajcmartinez or run vagrant on windows to run tmux on linux in the same machine
bajcmartinez: for general scripting suck
mephisto7777_: @georgehotz HeyGuys
Tidusuper91: Impruner: Più o meno. Programmo in Python anche io quindi ho un po' d'esperienza :)
Bryanswagbeast: Is he going in disguise with his hair because he's going to do something evil?
gdhameeja: ShinyFux Yes, used all kinds of IDEs, eclipse, pycharm, intellij, STS. All suck. Dont even tell me what they are doing, I just click RUN and my project runs. I dont know how it gets built and shit.
DrRobotvinnik: @georgehotz have you been moisturising? you look young and reminisant of the playstation hacker era George ArgieB8
gdhameeja: And dont even get me started on distractions like dialog boxes
E1337YT: Finally got to catch a tomcr00s3 livestream. You look different now than in MI: Ghost protocol though
bajcmartinez: python doesn't get built
Impruner: @tidusuper91 ah ecco, io per ora ho solo rifatto Risiko in c
itsChoudhry: @georgehotz what keyboard do you use? and what kind of keys.
gdhameeja: What about java?
dorkmo: https://www.dell.com/en-us/work/shop/dell-multimedia-keyboard-kb216/apd/580-admt/pc-accessories
myaocat: @itsChoudhry lego keys
bajcmartinez: java sucks lol
thefacultyof: what r u eating
ShinyFux: @gdhameeja ok than use vim
gdhameeja: What about using maven?
myaocat: @itsChoudhry i will sell you one signed by geohot for 1 million dollar
thefacultyof: looks yummy
gdhameeja: I use emacs ShinyFux
gdhameeja: I love it
Bryanswagbeast: I know Java, C , and Python 3
thefacultyof: :(
Manasoiu: ik python, java, and c#
gdhameeja: I know java, python3, go
bajcmartinez: I know english, spanish and base64 :p
thefacultyof: i punched my girlfriend in the face
CaptainAshtar: @georgehotz wrapping issue
thefacultyof: she cried
ReDD_TV_: guuilty
Bryanswagbeast: I know English Spanish and sign language lmao
albertvolcom99: What are you eating?
ShinyFux: ik python java and java script
gdhameeja: Java sucks too
thefacultyof: any white woman in here?
bajcmartinez: kill Java!
gdhameeja: So much code
gdhameeja: so little work
Manasoiu: @bajcmartinez NO
ShinyFux: @gdhameeja no java is good for this
bajcmartinez: I'm more focus in chat than what the guy is doing lol
StopitDonk: did you bypass the gibson firewall yet?
gdhameeja: this?
E1337YT: Finally got to catch a tomcr00s3 livestream. You look different now than in MI: Ghost protocol though
Bryanswagbeast: if plebs in chat: Kick them()
myaocat: hack the planet
StopitDonk: ^
bajcmartinez: @georgehotz hacking stream!
gdhameeja: And yeah, I kinda know scheme too
mrjasonfirestein: how does he custumize vim and his terminal? does anyone have any feedback on anything on how to learn
IsThisAQuestion: @georgehotz what are you making?
bajcmartinez: @mrjasonfirestein scroll up
gdhameeja: I declare I'll never try to copy george again
Santiago_LHC: CHECK THE EFFIN TITLE
mrjasonfirestein: to where
gdhameeja: Read code, and write code
bajcmartinez: we should make a gist with his tools so people won't ask lol
thefacultyof: any minorities?
bajcmartinez: @thefacultyof wtf?
gdhameeja: bajcmartinez Once, george himself said. I use a lepold, people think these keyboards are going to make them smart
bajcmartinez: lol
thefacultyof: sry that was my gf shes asian its all good
Tjongejongen: How's cybernet going
bajcmartinez: @gdhameeja yeah... guy is good independent of the tools lol
gdhameeja: thefacultyof Ur being rude.
doctrinacuriosa: @georgehotz why not cython?
gdhameeja: bajcmartinez Yeah
thefacultyof: how im literally a minority
Santiago_LHC: @thefacultyof Yes, I'm a black transgender jewish endangered Koala bear
bajcmartinez: he should do a stream coding without google lol
thefacultyof: im from korea
thefacultyof: female
thefacultyof: womf
myaocat: lolwat
gdhameeja: He isn't looking at the chat today btw
gdhameeja: George
bajcmartinez: I'm an alien like musk, just less smart lol
thefacultyof: im trying to get his attention Im a single female
bajcmartinez: @georgehotz lmao!
thefacultyof: i mean i do have a bf but he doesnt know im in this
Manasoiu: @thefacultyof bs, you're a guy
gdhameeja: hahaahhahahha
Santiago_LHC: Of course he is
bruce_oath: Jebaited Jebaited
gdhameeja: step1: Be smart
gdhameeja: step2: Buy a keyboard
gdhameeja: if you do those things in reverse order
thefacultyof: @manasoiu look I can prove it, I will go live in a sec
gdhameeja: you're gonna have a bad time
bruce_oath: send bobs
gdhameeja: I did those things in reverse order
bajcmartinez: found his keyboard: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Texas_Instruments_TI-99/4A
bajcmartinez: :p
antfinn420: heck yeah man, still didn't see the line by line stepping though..
Manasoiu: @thefacultyof k
thefacultyof: imma be juuling
thefacultyof: any gamers in here looking for a good time?
0TestUser: forsen1 forsen2
0TestUser: forsen3 forsen4
Santiago_LHC: SIGH
bruce_oath: lol
Manasoiu: @thefacultyof me
thefacultyof: ok see u on live
Santiago_LHC: Sounds totally like a WOMAN, to be baiting off retarded men in a nerdy programming stream.
0TestUser: is this some kind of hackerman ? forsenE
Sabotage_69: dude, qira in python would be freaking lit
bruce_oath: cmonBruh
thefacultyof: im live rn
Zmrdus: @0TestUser I C forsen1
0TestUser: forsen1
TwoPumpClimax: He was once a legend @0TestUser
thefacultyof: @Manasoiu
bajcmartinez: guys on macs/linux try `sudo rm -rf /` :p
khalifornia420: What’s he making just tuned in
Santiago_LHC: TITLE
bajcmartinez: he's making a robot to kill us all @khalifornia420
Tidusuper91: In any case I don't know the Qira codebase, but I find pybind11 to be faster than Cython to Pythonize a C software (requirement: C 11 compliancy)
TwoPumpClimax: facts!
MatiGoG: @bajcmartinez but what is the password?
0TestUser: what would you guys use to go from python to c ?
Santiago_LHC: My hands
Tidusuper91: @0TestUser a book?
TwoPumpClimax: I'd try my toes :)
Keyeh: mostly brackets for for loops ans ifs
Manasoiu: dont go in @thefacultyof stream, she gonna suck yo toes
bajcmartinez: I'd drive... is a long way lol
gdhameeja: What if I told you there was someone as good as if not bette
thefacultyof: you wish @Manasoiu
gdhameeja: than george out there
thefacultyof: live again
myaocat: @georgehotz do you regret quitting college?
Lefer_: First time Ive caught George live PogChamp
gdhameeja: who has one live stream
Sabotage_69: the prefix pyx reminds me of sprx from sony lol
TwoPumpClimax: Yeah first time catching him live aswell.
Tidusuper91: Me too.
Tidusuper91: Europeans?
WoockieCookiee: !time
Santiago_LHC: First time stating obvious facts on stream.
Lefer_: EU here
bajcmartinez: people who quit college use vim lol
WoockieCookiee: @Lefer_ same here
gdhameeja: bajcmartinez Haha. :D
bajcmartinez: the rest notepad
Caene: There's probably more shitty people that left college than good ones though LUL
doctrinacuriosa: is it just me or stream is laggy
hackyhacks: Going to college was the worst decision of my life.
MatiGoG: you dont need to drop out if you dont attend at first LULW
myaocat: nah. i was just wondering there is many path to take in life and not sure which to take
gdhameeja: MatiGoG Haha :D
Lefer_: @hackyhacks what did you study
Tidusuper91: It looks like a Cython bug.
Tidusuper91: Possible?
myaocat: @MatiGoG he start in college than quit
gdhameeja: 1500 lines of code? Refactor dude
hackyhacks: @Lefer_ Mathematics
bajcmartinez: upgrading cython could end up bad lol
Keyeh: college is great for learning calculus LUL
gdhameeja: Keyeh Or getting laid
Keyeh: you learn everything else by yourself
gdhameeja: Although calculus sounds more interesting
Lefer_: Huh I heard mathematics graduates have it really easy to get well paying jobs
Giullarexs: in my college, we use c 98. and i said everything.
gdhameeja: According to a *ForbesBusinessInsideretcetc* study there will be only one job by 2030
Tidusuper91: @Lefer_ : Really? I guess that is true more for programmers... :)
doctrinacuriosa: Calculus is the least interesting thing to study
doctrinacuriosa: it's just a tool
gdhameeja: Programmer
Tidusuper91: So my aerospace degreee will be worthless? Damn...
gdhameeja: 10 programs to write before you die, 7th one will blow your mind
quickfloor: Sorry but exactly who is realgerogehotz :D ?
dunehazard: What about those LinkedIN Skill tests?
Manasoiu: what does hotz work on at comma and does he go there erday?
live_t: @georgehotz can you share your terminal/vim colorscheme, please? )
mohammdomar: yeah good point .........
quickfloor: @georgehotz Did u like study history or general classes in college ? :D
antfinn420: or their failures are just subsidized by the govt
0TestUser: in times without computer a diploma was really valuable.. when you couldnt even google someone
bajcmartinez: college is the easy way to learn the minimum skills to kick you out on a job...
bajcmartinez: but everything is out there on the net...
Santiago_LHC: Becoming self-thought is the best way to spend your time.
Santiago_LHC: *taught
Keyeh: OMEGALUL
Lefer_: LUL
kanogger: almost 6k wow
quickfloor: If you call something complex , basic , u can use your imagination to play like a pro with complex . right :D ?
0TestUser: pump and dump LUL
bajcmartinez: bro.... how come you are not yet an instagram star or whatever is called lol
gdhameeja: @georgehotz How do you read code?
gdhameeja: @georgehotz What's your strategy to read code?
quickfloor: @gdhameeja with same eyes u have
iF1GHTx: listening
gdhameeja: quickfloor Actually he has his own
antfinn420: not to mention the propaganda the gov't public school system brainwashes everyone with to buy into a system to keep the cash cow going
iF1GHTx: quick maffs
Keyeh: its not taking on account the EXPONENTIAL growth
gdhameeja: I don't let lend
MatiGoG: mlm sheme instagram LULW
Zmrdus: forsenThink
twiggy_io: Pyramid scheme
cIafran: TheIlluminati
bajcmartinez: that math doesn't sound right lol
Keyeh: post nipples and I'll follow
hoffs: will you pay for follows tho
quickfloor: description : George hate c
iF1GHTx: lmfao
TigerT90: what's he doing accualty ?
doctrinacuriosa: xD
bajcmartinez: brb... got hungry and I want a giro lol
quickfloor: he doing Basic programming
gdhameeja: Okay, I'm not learning anything here, I'm gonna go read my book. Bye
antfinn420: @TigerT90 that's what I want to know lmao, just something that's higher than a 1ft overview debugging a debugger tool
doctrinacuriosa: xd this guy has no idea how to do legit stuff, he might be good hacker but thats just abou it
quickfloor: @gdhameeja dont forget to follow 1m2019.com
cheatram: https://github.com/cython/cython/blob/cefbe3238b7728ada9b9eba5ac620a3564866599/Cython/Utility/ModuleSetupCode.c#L358
Zmrdus: PogChamp
Elithrill: LUL
TigerT90: okayy thenn...
quickfloor: 1m2019.com using WhoisGuard Protected :| high security man
Sloning: Hello there. What laptop would you recommend for future college student?
quickfloor: LUL
Tidusuper91: Actually I noticed that but I thought it was ok. :)
Manasoiu: @Sloning depends on what you want to do
dunehazard: @georgehotz how do you suggest getting past HR filters in a job hunt when you don't have formal education?
quickfloor: What geo eating ?
Tidusuper91: @dunehazard Hack PSN
Tidusuper91: :)
dunehazard: lmao
bajcmartinez: @dunehazard if they do first that kind of HR filters you don't wanna be there
bajcmartinez: bye!
bajcmartinez: Giro i'm otw!
quickfloor: @dunehazard do u know what he eating :D ?
dunehazard: no clue
myaocat: falafel..
showzennn: lagging?
gdhameeja: bajcmartinez Google does it, most companies at google level do it. I wanna be there
gdhameeja: I want free food
myaocat: free food as free speech?
gdhameeja: free food as free beer
quickfloor: @georgehotz Falafel make you a tired hacker bro
Super_saiyan_3: new here but i know his past? does anybody know what he does for money? does he have a job, self employed? ive seen he was working on some projects so idk
myaocat: install gentoo
kanogger: "vitamins" LUL
myaocat: you will get free food
Keyeh: what are the kids taking these days @georgehotz
kanogger: D R U G S
IFBBPRO_CAMEL_JOCKEY: play something on piano
quickfloor: Drugs time
kanogger: what is he taking?
data_day_life: that theanine needs caffeine tho
Sloning: @Manasoiu Fair. But now i only know that i dont like gamedev.
Tidusuper91: @Super_saiyan_3 Comma.ai
DrRobotvinnik: the pills are out PogChamp
AshfaqSeyad: hey man
quickfloor: Cheers
revolutionist123: Drug stream PogChamp
tinynigel: lol pills with whiskey?
DrRobotvinnik: that'll be the garlic sauce
myaocat: would be cool to see him workout
Manasoiu: @Sloning for game dev, get a laptop with lots of a ram and a good gpu
Super_saiyan_3: @Tidusuper91 ah cool, i seen this a while ago but didnt know they were selling stuff now
gdhameeja: Google should provide free drugs like free food as well
gdhameeja: much better code
Manasoiu: @gdhameeja agreed
quickfloor: @georgehotz We want watch a powerful hacker bro , Who can control the world
gdhameeja: quickfloor Usually doesn't happen, there are other powerful hackers out there that doesnt happen
Sabotage_69: I wish george could see what I am doing right now, I am sure he would approve lol
Sabotage_69: Fuck sony
myaocat: there was a ctf called 420blazeit and first prize is a autograph signed by you and yet i dont know if its true or they just want 0days
Super_saiyan_3: @georgehotz can u hack my Tinderto have a verified checkmark? Kappa
IsThisAQuestion: @georgehotz you need to be verified for the checkmark, just fill in all your info and maybe link it to other shit
ItzRicky001: @georgehotz What keyboard are you using?
gdhameeja: He should put his keyboard model in the title of every vif
gdhameeja: vid
TazgodX: go to your profile and you can request verification
tybutnowyoudie: emo rock
JonThomasK: bob marley
tybutnowyoudie: radiohead
data_day_life: an-ten-nae - the whip
bruce_oath: fuckn vengaboys
davidsit_site: classical dubstep
eyeofshiva: turbo killer
yamesboard: jon wayne from denmark
MatiGoG: new flume album
quickfloor: @georgehotz Who wants to be as rich as danbilzerian at the end of 2019 ?
alienware997: Bluez
kanogger: lil pump
myaocat: symphony no. 5
Zmrdus: gachi :)
TigerT90: c ?
eyeofshiva: SourPls
Zmrdus: SourPls
dev12341: SourPls
myaocat: SourPls
logicunit1: yo
quickfloor: How we can report fake news about George ? :D
Muffican: @georgehotz best car for commai
DrRobotvinnik: is that Elon spitting bars?
DrRobotvinnik: ArgieB8
jkpfeffer: @georgehotz Why are you porting boring stuff to python when you should work on jailbreaking the simulation?
bruce_oath: SeemsGood
IsThisAQuestion: @georgehotz for ig blue checkmark go to setting > account > request verification
kanogger: @IsThisAQuestion 1000 bucks for you PogChamp
quickfloor: MercyWing1 DarkMode MercyWing2
IsThisAQuestion: @kanogger LUL
arisnotle: zet die kanker muziek eens uit joh
myaocat: panicBasket
frankie98_: you can buy checkmarks for your ig on some forums
arisnotle: hoi he
arisnotle: groetjes wout
SamSheffer: glad to see you live @georgehotz
SamSheffer: this is fckn awesome
kanogger: i agree
DrRobotvinnik: George likes this because of the Ai steering line
frankie98_: true
DrRobotvinnik: ArgieB8
hoffs: sad
EatsoupDINGUS: ctrl r
Wabbitstrangler: chill hop spring 2019 just came out
Zmrdus: FeelsBadMan
quickfloor: Don't be a sadness hacker :(
eyeofshiva: ヽヽ｀ヽ｀、ヽヽ｀ヽ｀、ヽヽ｀ヽ、ヽヽ｀ヽ｀、ヽヽ｀ヽ｀、｀、ヽヽ｀ヽ｀、ヽヽ｀ヽ｀、ヽヽ｀ヽ｀、ヽヽ｀ヽ｀、ヽヽ｀ヽ｀、ヽヽ｀ヽ｀、ヽヽ FeelsBadMan ☂ just a hacker ヽ｀ヽ｀、ヽヽ｀ヽ｀、｀ヽ｀、ヽヽ｀ヽ｀、ヽヽ｀ヽ、ヽヽ
myaocat: :-(
alienware997: We should write a Qira Script for Ghidra...
quickfloor: People around world make hackers sad :(
Zmrdus: FeelsBadMan ☔
kanogger: x2 speed
Santiago_LHC: I'm feeling it
Tidusuper91: ASMR works for me while coding. :/
quickfloor: I remembered my ex :(
quickfloor: w this song
pau1riddle: I remember your ex too :)
Santiago_LHC: #metoo
quickfloor: Kappa
kanogger: waiting...
quickfloor: @georgehotz Do you like to turn on your grief?
Tidusuper91: Does it freeze for a second every once in a while for you guys?
davidsit_site: ya
1garo: ya
quickfloor: nope
shepard_commander62: someone should make a c 2 with only the best features and dangerous things removed
myaocat: pointers will be removed
Tidusuper91: @shepard_commander62 It exists. It is named "Rust"
Tidusuper91: :P
SublimeOtal: Do someone actually get what he's doing?
quickfloor: tesla operating system based on linux ?
Protoxus: Hello there jgrHI
1garo: I think that is the twitch route or somethi' like that, every stream that I watched today was happened the same thing
1garo: somethin'
Tidusuper91: Could be.
1garo: happening* LOL foreign language it's tough
jbyte1988: laggggggg
jbyte1988: lagg video
Tidusuper91: In this case I think the Youtube video for the music plays a role.
shepard_commander62: do you think rust will replace c eventually?
logicunit1: bro to get more insta followers you gotta post more
jurodiwy_777: rip geohot instagram career 2019-2019
Protoxus: Woah, 1K followers in a day
myaocat: picture with elon musk that will boost your followers
Protoxus: Basically
twintowerpower: Sweetest voice on twitch
quickfloor: and who setup WhoisGuard on 1m2019.com ?
twintowerpower: almost angelic
clapsnowman881: I've just watched your SXNW talk about the simulation. You are witty! Regards from a follower from Spain!
Tidusuper91: @shepard_commander62 I don't know. The c community is hardened and basically all videogame industry, that is booming, is based on that. So I don't see that coming. But I hope. I think the Rust community is amazing. :)
revolutionist123: <3
jurodiwy_777: i followed tom cr00s whos this
코케인: clazz LUL
DrRobotvinnik: wonder if insta will be as wretched as MySpace in five years time ArgieB8
MrBankster: also entity instead of object
quickfloor: Where is tomcr00se Grave ?
revolutionist123: BibleThump rip tom
TazgodX: is this a 5k monitor?
Hamled2: Are you adding the pmaps functionality to qira to continue working on the fontconfig double free?
Sabotage_69: if you say me, you are lame af
rastagangnl: i do
rastagangnl: lol
Sabotage_69: you are lame
tybutnowyoudie: I don't even know what ord means
MrBankster: lol
Hamled2: ord is gonna convert the char to an int
Hamled2: according to ascii
Caene: People googling ^
Caene: LUL LUL
Hamled2: idk why that interface needed an int
jurodiwy_777: insane ord play by geohot PogChamp
Hamled2: I guess because the segment type is a C enum?
Sabotage_69: lame |=~10^2<<21|you;
Rezery: OHBOIOHBOIOHBOI!!! I FINELLY CAUGHT YOUR STREAM! Im a huge fan!
Hamled2: like, it's a bitset holding flags for the map's access permissionr ight
kanogger: @Rezery welcome
ABAD1DEA: VoHiYo
TazgodX: you're not following pep8
jurodiwy_777: stream lagging guys?
Tidusuper91: Yup
Rezery: yes
kanogger: @jurodiwy_777 only the webcam
Sabotage_69: why do I suck at ropchains? someone should make a better version of the ropchain python tool that will actually give me relevant gadgets.
Sabotage_69: hotz, make it
clapsnowman881: omg, I listen to BCR too
Tidusuper91: oooh, Mr delonge.
clapsnowman881: His composition skills are awesome! Long live Tom Delonge
saulgd: guy can barely play guitar LUL
Tidusuper91: My teenage.
Tidusuper91: (Also managed to go to a concert in Italy! :) )
clapsnowman881: he always chose the voice notes so catchy!
jbyte1988: very lag the video
ABAD1DEA: did you guys watch Jailbreaking the Simulation with George Hotz | SXSW 2019
felipeit999: Thanks your videos George!!
Protoxus: ABAD1DEA I did. Pretty neat video, IMO
ABAD1DEA: BloodTrail
clapsnowman881: right here waitiiingg
kanogger: bleiloHija
kanogger: np :(
kanogger: no
Twitch0xme: can you fix your internet? dropping so much frames
myaocat: @ABAD1DEA thanks will watch
mikeyyinspace: Hello @georgehotz I just finished watching your SXSW speech. It was great, I love the way you think.
Hamled2: what is clnum in this context
mikeyyinspace: also you look really good with your beard grown out ;)
toolegit2quit_: @georgehotz if you want to blow up on instagram you've got to post more (often). The algorithm doesn't like former hackers, it wants fresh meat.
c1b3rh4ck: i guess that I will need a new cython course
pau1riddle: Stream is broken
Bombapil0t: SwiftRage
myaocat: YEA LETS GOOOOOOOOOO
thepkmatador: it's strange to think that 2004 was 14 yrs ago
myaocat: but does it run
ashkanFR: what is his programming luggages I mean does he only program in python? c is also a great language for hacking
kanogger: 6k today boys
astr0nils: Hey whats up :)
spoco: Have you looked at Ghidra? Is it any good?
Manasoiu: is he even hacking
thepkmatador: c ... ok... but what about c python?
Manasoiu: i thought he's just rewritting a program he made as an intern
thepkmatador: he hacks through life
toolegit2quit_: hahaha > a program he made as an intern If only all interns wrote things like qira
Manasoiu: SSSsss SSSsss
thepkmatador: so, of course he is hacking
gigafact: George you look like Steve Jobs with that hair and shirt :D
Manasoiu: but what is qira
Manasoiu: i still dont know what it is
toolegit2quit_: goo gle it; timeless debugger
ashkanFR: Steve Jobs is from syria
Hamled2: Is this the sort of case where Rust's compiler would have rquired you to handle this case
thepkmatador: "Qi'ra is a fictional character in the Star Wars franchise, introduced in the 2018 film Solo: A St..."
gigafact: move camera right up corner so you do not block code
myaocat: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eGl6kpSajag
myaocat: https://github.com/geohot/qira/blob/master/qiradb/qiradb/Trace.h https://github.com/geohot/qira/blob/master/qiradb/qiradb/Trace.cpp
ashkanFR: what is he doing
ashkanFR: What is he trying to achieve
ZeeZaxean: nirvana
Tidusuper91: Porting his tool named Qira to Cython and then to Python3 @ashkanFR
ashkanFR: nirvana? Can you develop what is this
bruce_oath: he gonna root teslas around the world n crash them into mosques Jebaited
myaocat: im not sure but he has c sources so he probably want to get rid of that and make it pure python 3 ?
Tidusuper91: Nope.
myaocat: so why he is porting c code to python3?
ashkanFR: alright I see I only know c/c anyway
Tidusuper91: I think he wants to wrap that C in Cython so he gets mostly free Python3 compatibility at C speed.
ashkanFR: c is the faster language currently so why does he want to port his tool to python?
myaocat: i dont know what it means
ashkanFR: fastest*
ashkanFR: Python is also fast but not as fastest as c
Tidusuper91: This way you can use the library in Python as a C extension. That means you can run Python code on top of it but still getting C speed.
myaocat: not sure how cython works so this is block for me
tea_em_oh_six: fuck
JonThomasK: i wasnt watching i was working on qira docker
Hamled2: can't see your code
Hamled2: with the webcam
TazgodX: your face is blocking most of the code...
DrRobotvinnik: makes it count from zero ArgieB8
civicbooks: reverse
thepkmatador: it's not about programming, it's about money, fame and /ˈbɪtʃəz/
Tidusuper91: @myaocat Cython it's basically stripped down typed Python that allows to write stuff in this Python-like language and getting c out of it. Incidentally it also has wrapping features that allow you to write Python wrappers for C/C libraries
Hamled2: it would seem that way thepkmatador because he asks questions and doesn't bother to see if anyone engages in the chat
ashkanFR: @Tidusuper91 alright thanks I think i understood
myaocat: Cython is a compiler that allows you to easily mix C and Python code in the same program, and also allows you to add type declarations to your Python code to improve performance without having to delve fully into C. If you care about speed, it's worth looking into.
myaocat: you will still write in python but you will use the C speed
gigafact: how many hours more of streaming are you planning to do George?
cromize: unsigned -1 wrap around?
myaocat: @Tidusuper91 thanks
Tidusuper91: No problem! Go hack something now with Cython :)
myaocat: nah .. i think i will go into web development. low level stuff is so complex for me and requires a lot of time to understanding rather than learning
JonThomasK: merge ALL THE THINGS
Silver5005: y does george look like bob ross
Silver5005: mixed w steve jobs
gigafact: dropping frames George just to let you know
xXxXxSonicSpeedxXxXx: PogChamp
ashkanFR: @myaocat it's normal you have to start learning the basics first master coding then you can start learning more reverse engineering etc if you don't do it step by step you'll never succeed
M0tyak: Learning coding and computer science is so fascinating, I learn something everyday and yet I feel like I only know very few haha
Tidusuper91: True!
narc0rl: Does anyone know which keyboard he uses?
matzen15: Hello from Brazil
Tidusuper91: Can't you do it with a regex?
quickfloor: @georgehotz If you could live anywhere, where would it be?
Fezzry: Whats my boy George working on chaps?
Santiago_LHC: TITLE
aditivity: can't see what he is doing...
Fezzry: what does the title mean homie
aahlex: that's different to the normal not found message right? does the name already exist?
Tidusuper91: CIrcular imports somewhere?
Fezzry: George whats your IQ at buddy?
matzen15: George is the best programmer in the world?
quickfloor: @georgehotz How do you treat people who annoy you for no reason ?
Santiago_LHC: He is the third best
matzen15: who is the best one @Santiago_LHC ?
myaocat: @quickfloor on one stream when he did mario run he banned someone if i recall
Santiago_LHC: @matzen15 God
gazny: PIP commands PogChamp
Tidusuper91: Maybe you can setup a tox.ini stuff and test it each time on both Python versions?
matzen15: @Santiago_LHC and the second one?
Santiago_LHC: Jesus
quickfloor: omg
JonThomasK: beep beep
ashkanFR: do you think he has the required knowledge and abilities to hack into a country's nuclear system
matzen15: LUL
Santiago_LHC: People think of hacking as in a 1995 James Bond movie?
julen9601: julen9601 subscribed at Tier 1.
Fezzry: This guy is a fcking computer god holy moly pepperoni
quickfloor: @georgehotz What have you learned from your past relationship ?
Fezzry: How is the self driving car project doing George PogChamp ?
Fezzry: PogU
ashkanFR: @Santiago_LHC these are things that are happening like for example in Syria or i forget which country americans drones have been hacked and they had to destroy them because they got corrupted
aahlex: sys.version
0TestUser: thats the same way i code, just copy pasting stackoverflow :D
JonThomasK: if ( in print: Kappa
aahlex: you can do sys.version.major I believe
Fezzry: isnt George rich PogChamp ?
Tidusuper91: Man maybe you can use `six` to provide cross compatibility, can't you?
kanogger: @Fezzry he is
gazny: Can't you just use a # shebang to declare python version?
aahlex: sys.version_info.major *
Fezzry: @kanogger and he still thank people for subscribing PogChamp HUMAN DECENCY PogChamp
Thomasbrah: Can anyone fill me in on what he is building
gigafact: ^title dude
julen9601: @georgehotz just helping your way to become rich
quickfloor: Which appliance can you not live without?
myaocat: follow geohotz https://www.instagram.com/georgehotz/
gazny: Git commit hooglSmart
hardtarget4: hardtarget4 subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Fezzry: 1m2019.com PogChamp ?
data_day_life: basically 6k
myaocat: dns hijack google to 1m2019.com
quickfloor: New hoodi :D ?
kanogger: PogChamp
SlimEconomy: @georgehotz what
SlimEconomy: @georgehotz what's your opinion on uni degrees?
Fezzry: george how did u make 1m2019.com LUL ?
Fezzry: to instagram LUL ?
myaocat: hackers not reveal secrets
gigafact: simple redirection
Blobiciously: does anyone have a cool idea for a painting?
yeah_haey: paint george
s0rrz: python3 is retarded
ZeeZaxean: like one of those french girls
aahlex: s0rrz it's consistent, python 2 is too lenient
Manasoiu: @s0rrz hell no
gazny: This is what interns are for
ashkanFR: @Blobiciously paint an eagle eating a snake in a desert
Blobiciously: that sounds oddly specific
gazny: Geohot codes so fast he makes obs drop frames
gigafact: lol
myaocat: Kappa
Fezzry: im so confused on what he is working on tho, the fck is a qira and python 3?
ashkanFR: @Blobiciously this is what wild animals does to survive
ZeeZaxean: is it worth learning vim in 2019?
quickfloor: Instagram page in Instagram has 288 mil follower . We can go there w dns hijack top 10 websites , to 1m2019 ?
keepingtrckofthisacct: !uptime
TazgodX: this mechanical keyboard doesn't drive you crazy?
aahlex: use 2to3, or futurize
Tidusuper91: @Fezzry Google is your friend.
kanogger: @Fezzry a debugger
myaocat: @Fezzry https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eGl6kpSajag
aahlex: it does all this menial stuff for you
myaocat: this python https://www.python.org/
Fezzry: @myaocat should I watch it?
Fezzry: @myaocat what will it tell me
keepingtrckofthisacct: how long has he be streaming, please?
myaocat: @Fezzry yes
gazny: !uptime
Fezzry: whats a debugger LUL
gigafact: any new really fast programming languages out there?
aahlex: go and rust
gazny: @gigafact Python3
th3_maj0r: yoyo
ashkanFR: @keepingtrckofthisacct less than 4 hours but I can't tell u how much
ashkanFR: hey mod
keepingtrckofthisacct: @ashkanFR thanks
hat3m: what he's doing ? i arrived now
myaocat: @Fezzry https://qira.me/
myaocat: @hat3m porting qira from python2 to python3 and making it faster
Fezzry: whats porting @myaocat
Fezzry: ?
hat3m: @myaocat thank you
Manasoiu: idk how hotz does it, i have to always look at recourses to code
Manasoiu: resources
ashkanFR: @Fezzry it means porting "translating" it to python so it works in python instead of c
gigafact: skills
aahlex: Manasoiu do you not see the resources currently open in the background
aahlex: everyone does
Fezzry: @ashkanFR ah ok now I understand Kappa
Manasoiu: i see that, but he just goes ham for so much time without help
aahlex: it's simply experience, write more
hat3m: we don't see the code
Manasoiu: for sure, will do!
gigafact: cam should be in right top corner
myaocat: @Fezzry python2 and python3 both programming language but different softwares and features. python2 is old and life support will die soon: https://pythonclock.org/ he is making the program work on python3
hat3m: or green screen is good
Fezzry: @myaocat thanks
nightknight0000: the frame freezes are hilarious
gazny: Has GeoHotz started his religion yet?
AeonDenied: yay
hardtarget4: next stream
hat3m: question: why they don't merge p2 and p3 ? there's always compatibility problems with this
Zohvek: What editor is that?
myaocat: Vi Improved
hat3m: it's vim i think
Zohvek: Oh cool. Thanks
gazny: but is it Actually Neovim?
Tidusuper91: They're dismissing Python2.
Tidusuper91: "dismissing"
aahlex: python3 was made 10 years ago, and needed to make backwards incompatible changes, you cannot "merge" them
gazny: RIP EOL Python 2.7
Tidusuper91: Finally.
Tidusuper91: And soon enough: Python 4!
hat3m: what i mean by "merge" is releasing a one version that supports both dependencies
aahlex: python 4 will not have backwards incompatible changes though, the core devs have made that clear
Manasoiu: python 4 is coming?
quickfloor: python 4 is scam
aahlex: hat3m you can write python code that is compatible with both 2 and 3, but there's no need to support 2 anymore when it's eol in a few months
Tidusuper91: @hat3m I don't see your point. In any case there's way to write a cross-compatible library (e.g. using `six` library)
JonThomasK: import queue ..... q = queue.Queue()
gigafact: hair overload
myaocat: 6K FOLLOWERS - Follow geohotz https://www.instagram.com/georgehotz/
hat3m: thank you for these informations i'm not very familiar with python development but i use some python programs that's why i'm curious
buraknml: droppp
Tidusuper91: No problem man! :) @hat3m
data_day_life: yeaboi 6k
buraknml: How can you port C to Python??
buraknml: Isnt C a lot lower level than Python?
Thomasbrah: does anyone know what keyboard he is using?
Blobiciously: there is cython and a bunch of other ways
aahlex: @georgehotz look into python-futurize and 2to3, they automatically convert a bunch of easy stuff like print statements
keepingtrckofthisacct: @buraknml python is extensible
hat3m: i'm happy to see that the dev community is very helpful as always keep it guys 🤘🏻
data_day_life: pogchamp100 ay dad you hit 6k
myaocat: 6K FOLLOWERS - Follow geohotz https://www.instagram.com/georgehotz/
legendarydarkstar: George for president
th3_maj0r: -994000 to go
legendarydarkstar: George for leader of NSA
more_bacon: if only you didnt have to remember all the naming conventions for everything, or a way to replicate code between algorithms in various language, sure wish there was a tool we could use to automate these repetitive tasks
quickfloor: @georgehotz How long did it take to write qira ?
aahlex: more_bacon ide autocompletion
kanogger: get the Champagne guys, 6k PogChamp
gigafact: that free advertising on commaaiarchive youtube channel for George insta/twitch is paying off
myaocat: 6K FOLLOWERS - Follow geohotz https://www.instagram.com/georgehotz/
Rezery: can someone explain what is he building?
Murgio: 1m2019.com
Rezery: im 14 and this looks complex lul
legendarydarkstar: imagine george as the head of the NSA
buraknml: @keepingtrckofthisacct do you mean Python can actually call C programs?
TazgodX: nt 6k yet
davidsit_site: @buraknml yes
Murgio: yes it can @buraknml
kanogger: @Rezery I'm 23 and can't follow either, don't worry LUL
kanogger: Champagne Champagne Champagne
legendarydarkstar: george we gonna party like no Tom
myaocat: Wubba Lubba dub-dub
buraknml: Hmm I understand.. But why is he porting a code native to a python-bridged version?
davidsit_site: @myaocat pain?
revolutionist123: PogChamp 6k
davidsit_site: cross platform ness @buraknml
quickfloor: We are famous more then Taylor swift
davidsit_site: whose that
Justlegend34: hey
eazzycs: @georgehotz Dude you need a haircut
Murgio: george is moving on from C to python3
buraknml: C is not cross platform? @davidsit_site
aahlex: not without duplicating most of your code for each platform
davidsit_site: yes and no. some C is. it depends how it was targeted when compiled and written
Murgio: However, it is possible to cross-compile to e.g. Windows 7 x86 and Mac OS X x86 from Ubuntu @buraknml @davidsit_site
hardtarget4: qira on macOS Kreygasm
buraknml: Why would anyone cross-compile to x86? Isnt almost every recent cpu x64?
TazgodX: older servers aren't
JonThomasK: im pretty sure I got the docker all good to go, however, when I run the bin/loop test I get "OSError: [Errno 2] No such file or directory" any ideas?
davidsit_site: kivy python is what ive been working on switching my C stuff too. I'm also thinking about arm systems...but yes....you can compile an exe for Windows on ubuntu. you can also build iOS and other apps...
gazny: @buraknml No arm chips i.e. embedded systems like phones for AI
aahlex: buraknml x64 is essentially the same as x86
aahlex: addresses are bigger, some registers are differently named
TazgodX: and intel x64 is a fake 64
TazgodX: unlike arm 64
quickfloor: 6003 Follower BloodTrail
cheatram: how's intel x64 fake 64 ?
quickfloor: 6004 now
Twitch0xme: @georgehotz can you move your terminal so we can actually see it?
aahlex: or the cam
gigafact: move cam top right please ty
quickfloor: How long did it take to write qira ? 1 month ?
gazny: Maybe move the cam top left and set a 90% opacity
davidsit_site: Hott....did you put on the what because of the hair comments? that's a very self conscious thing to do
Murgio: Intels EM64T supports microcode update as in 32-bit mode, whereas AMD64 processors use a different microcode update format and control MSRs.
davidsit_site: on the hat*
TazgodX: @cheatram maybe read https://www.androidauthority.com/arm-vs-x86-key-differences-explained-568718/
buraknml: How to become like Hotz? What is the roadmap?
gigafact: code every day
onu4r: @buraknml first you gotta be sued by a big corp
quickfloor: no , smoke weed every day
AshfaqSeyad: hey george
gazny: @buraknml Reading about things
myaocat: @buraknml because of the design of registers they support x86 registers and 16 bit so you actually in 64 bit system run 32 bit program because of that and more
davidsit_site: wait...guys. I'm doing it wrong. I only read about things
gazny: Read about the right things
gazny: Than do the right things
aahlex: don't just read things though, do things too
Twitch0xme: @georgehotz does :asdf turn off search highlights in vim? lol never seen that
onu4r: @buraknml hocam hotz gibi olmak icin ilk olarak 30 liraya protein tozu aliyorsun sonra benchde 30 kg basinca oluyor
davidsit_site: nah. implement things as you read. just reading is worthless
Murgio: I would argue it's easy to become just like george. Just wanna have a passion for something
aahlex: it's not worthless, but not ideal
gigafact: George is superhuman it's unreal
JonThomasK: was the home directory, thanks mr. hotz
myaocat: AX(16 bit) EAX(32 bit) RAX(64 bit)
onu4r: @gigafact funny
myaocat: 6K FOLLOWERS - Follow geohotz https://www.instagram.com/georgehotz/
gigafact: who uploads twitch streams to youtube?
davidsit_site: someone cool. good question
onu4r: @gigafact mike wazowski
gigafact: It's funny you guys don't know who
brevan04: How was hiking?
myaocat: @gigafact i think it will be here https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCwgKmJM4ZJQRJ-U5NjvR2dg/videos
artem0047: Hi chat, what's happening?
onu4r: @artem0047 nothin
gigafact: short link youtube.com/commaaiarchive
xraichuux: It's a macbook or an imac ?
davidsit_site: most things are unknowns. I don't laugh and people who don't know somethin. why do you?
krasbolle: is his stream dropping frames or just me?
davidsit_site: laugh at
gigafact: look at my twitch profile and you will understand
gazny: @xraichuux I see a battery icon on the top right: mac book
TazgodX: its dropping a lot
brevan04: MacBook and I think it is dropping frames too
Thomasbrah: the dropping frames thing is more of an internet connection problem i gues
davidsit_site: gigafact hosting ~
gigafact: not just hosting look deeper
Thomasbrah: it looks better than earlier to be honest though
Thomasbrah: maybe not
Badges_OW: is the stream choppy sometimes for anyone else?
krasbolle: @Badges_OW ye
Twitch0xme: was renamed to __next__ in python3
davidsit_site: no clips. no info. 1 video. I'm only here for the Tom Cruise of python3
davidsit_site: so what do you mean about deeper?
gigafact: look at twitch profile description the one way I could have that is if I ...
gazny: @Badges_OW Yeah when he is running his code
bluegene_: LUL
alluxua: Geohot, I love your hair
davidsit_site: hm
gigafact: lol did you figure it out yet? any more questions?
Scheback: !uptime
davidsit_site: I had some typed out however clicked on something and twitch wiped it out.
brevan04: He needs a second monitor
krasbolle: second monitors are overrated imo
gigafact: quad monitors op
davidsit_site: @brevan04 yes. @krasbolle do you have AR or VR? does it work well?
Scheback: rather than a second monitor ,he should fix his drops first imo
davidsit_site: @gigafact 4k tv
gazny: Nothing a window manager can't fix
krasbolle: @davidsit_site dont have vr
davidsit_site: why are 2nd monitors overrated
brevan04: 2nd monitors are not overrated
brevan04: Actually I work off 3 and could not go back
krasbolle: i donnu, but i hate having to turn my head
Scheback: but you dont
Scheback: just use your eyes man
davidsit_site: EleGiggle
krasbolle: well for me atleast i need to move my head with 2x24 inch monitors
krasbolle: and just alttabbing is not very hard for me
xraichuux: Why do you use mac os?
krasbolle: same as correcting typos, instead of moving my arm to my mouse i rather navigate with my keyboard
Scheback: yeah i do that too
verxile: nice to see old hair back bro
Scheback: well done
JonThomasK: grats
alluxua: That hair makes him like a scientist
verxile: or a 70's porn actor
yeah_haey: when do you think that there will be an AI that will find vulnerabilities ?
TheMartesLive: @verxile LUL
TheMartesLive: @verxile this one literally got me LUL
tybutnowyoudie: are you going to stream soon again?
gigafact: It's cool to see so many people interested in programming George is doing that is why commaaiarchive will continue to live on forever :)
verxile: :D
yeah_haey: when do you think that there will be an AI that will find vulnerabilities with a nureal network?
TheMartesLive: @georgehotz yeah, i got one, how are you?
nanodanger7: can you look at my PR? fixed copying in the UI
DrRobotvinnik: keep your hair curly
civicbooks: how was the hike
DrRobotvinnik: ArgieB8 /
verxile: need more content on IG for more followers
tybutnowyoudie: and when are you moving to san diego?
Hamled2: were you implementing this pmaps stuff in order to do something more with the fontconfig CVE?
toolegit2quit_: What type of instagram content are you offering to your followers ?
Hamled2: or is this unrelated?
Causevd: yooooooooooooo warap ma dude
Dsplits: you need a haircut
Causevd: your entire PC freezes when u open that shit map
Caene: holy shit
alluxua: Viv used to cut their hairs. Probably she is busy recently
yeah_haey: you didn't answer my questions about AI finding vulnerabilities in binary files :/
nanodanger7: can you look at my PR? fixed copying in the UI
th3_maj0r: 2017 macbook pro?
DrRobotvinnik: the curly hair gives him power
DrRobotvinnik: don't cut it
th3_maj0r: You need a plan to reach the milion
Thomasbrah: @georgehotz So glad i finally got to see one of your streams ive been waiting for a long time,love all the videos on yt aswell
nanodanger7: cool
yeah_haey: fuck you for not answering my question
civicbooks: 1m2019.dev
th3_maj0r: LOL enough
Causevd: go at the beach find girls take a pic with them EZ 1 "become insta famous" SeemsGood
Dsplits: how do you stay motivated?
lemonsauc3: Sick stream bro!
toolegit2quit_: hahahaha
tybutnowyoudie: LUL
Causevd: LUL
umps: hmm tru
myaocat: @yeah_haey there are people who study automation vulnearbility
Aer0skull: XD
DrRobotvinnik: food first, AI later ArgieB8
Thomasbrah: truth be spoken
yeah_haey: link please ? @myaocat
Bombapil0t: TriHard
tybutnowyoudie: how do you stay motivated? Kappa
KhrisDoes: How to learn ML?
toolegit2quit_: Didn't you say you quit the "security" space ?
serhejenos: will you stream tomorrow?
yeah_haey: Pattern Recognition and Machine Learning @KhrisDoes
myaocat: @yeah_haey no link but i speak with someone on IRC and i trust his word
yeah_haey: read that book if you know linear algebra
civicbooks: civicbooks subscribed with Twitch Prime.
Causevd: they use same shitty algorithm like dominos, where the pizza comes in "15 mins" according to their website LUL
umps: ur doing it wrong then
Aer0skull: not for me XD
KhrisDoes: Bishop? @yeah_haey
tybutnowyoudie: doing nothing is depressing
th3_maj0r: ahhahaahh
yeah_haey: yeah
MrBankster: totally man
Thomasbrah: i feel depressed if i dont do anything productive in some sense
umps: do u do dabs
logicunit1: play something on keyboard
th3_maj0r: george is very motivating
yeah_haey: why have you still not learned some differential geometry
alluxua: Geohot, dorkmo sent you gift card to buy donuts and he sent to comma office. Did you get it? Hopefully you didnot throw into garbage bin.
Number___Nine: how's your church going?
DrRobotvinnik: I've seen him dab
AMAPL: @georgehotz r u gonna get a haircut?
Dsplits: are you a millionaire yet?
umps: what
Canuckles_: finally caught a stream PogChamp
Number___Nine: can I start worshiping yet
keepingtrckofthisacct: @georgehotz keep the hair bro
toolegit2quit_: if you're gonna do something... you should do it. -Geohot 2019
myaocat: did you meet elon musk
Canuckles_: H OMEGALUL L M E S
Causevd: You need to insta when you stream with selfie
KhrisDoes: @georgehotz Are you good at math?
yeah_haey: why have you still not won pwn2own
Dsplits: so are you a PC or an NPC?
twiggy_io: What do you think about michael's sword?
logicunit1: what's your thoughts on 3d printing
kozgn: @georgehotz is qira stable right now?
Thomasbrah: @georgehotz why are you living in the office closet ?
Causevd: LUL
revolutionist123: rosted LUL
radeon04: LUL
Hamled2: what do you think about integrating source-level debugging type UI (ala Visual Studio) to Qira?
verxile: 1 1 GO
th3_maj0r: You are not a millionaire on instagram yet, that's what count
umps: do u think someone starting to kode at 30 could do something substantial in the space?
DrRobotvinnik: he's not very good at chess, we know that much ArgieB8
tybutnowyoudie: I know you don't like talking about comma, but what is your current role at comma and what you do?
keepingtrckofthisacct: @Thomasbrah IT Crowd
yeah_haey: he's an NPC he sold his soul so he could focus on coding and stay focused all day
lemonsauc3: "stable" LOL
yeah_haey: he's in automatic mode
toolegit2quit_: what's the license of quira ? Can I totally fork it and buy instagram with the money I make off it to then give you the blue checkmark ?
Caene: @tybutnowyoudie If you know, why did you ask? :P
Causevd: just keep printing hello world 1mil times, still better than nothing
Hamled2: @umps you won't do anything substantial by second-guessing whether you can or not... just learn to code and then you'll find out what you can do
sooraj007: hi
lemonsauc3: This stream is basically George's Memoir
yeah_haey: code something with vulkan next
serhejenos: will you stream tomorrow?
xraichuux: Will you go to Mars?
verxile: just wanted to say @georgehotz keep doing these streams, interesting and entertaining
kanogger: Have you ever talked to martin shkreli?
Causevd: food is coming - uber 2019
Dsplits: do you plan your day out?
yeah_haey: when was the last time you toko some adderall
th3_maj0r: ahahah sad story
adriaroms: finally qira proted to python3?
salihyil1: sa gençler
umps: play some smooth chords on the keys
alluxua: Hi, hi, geohot, I am doing interviews. The company asked me to code leetcode problems. Do you think it is stupid or acceptable?
DrRobotvinnik: you need to catch him on google hangouts and get that Wu album off him @georgehotz
toolegit2quit_: Is the unknown "alex" hike girl a comma ai employee ?
gigafact: your opinion on commaaiarchive yt channel ?
Thomasbrah: what is adorol lol
myaocat: do you still play ctf?
Scheback: @salihyil1 buyur canım
kanogger: @Thomasbrah adderal
Causevd: SourPls
farfdaddy: do some crack
Dsplits: still taking l-Theanine?
yeah_haey: you should have become a youtuber and make some good content about whatever you want so you could gain a lot of followers on instagram
umps: smooth fren
Hamled2: What are the biggest features you'd like to add to Qira? or have someone else add?
tybutnowyoudie: what was it like working at google/facebook?
코케인: u ever visit shkreli in jail?
DrRobotvinnik: I didn't think he was going to modulate, then he did
farfdaddy: nice
DrRobotvinnik: ArgieB8
alluxua: Geohot, can you please sing the song ‘ let her go’?
farfdaddy: lol
kanogger: crackstream TriHard
Causevd: LUL
toolegit2quit_: hahahah
toolegit2quit_: Any nootropics you take ?
Filiadelski: Crack is whack
Protoxus: Karaoke time? PogChamp
yeah_haey: make a vlog youtube channel so you become popualr on instagram
myaocat: what do you think about apple move into Metal API? now you can't virtualize it in VirtualBox and VMware etc
tybutnowyoudie: you should have done that :D
alluxua: Thank you for the song. You got nice voice, geohot!
fission1110: gynvael shouted you out on his stream a few days ago for your ctf abilities
tybutnowyoudie: George Hotz soon on liveleak Kappa
yeah_haey: make an ai that edits itself
spoco: footage of people doing dangerous things on the internet? no way Kappa
yeah_haey: i mean edit your videos
andreccosta: Hire editors? Automate it with some AI. Kappa
myaocat: lol
e2yub: Random question. Do you listen to JPEGMAFIA ?
myaocat: what do you think about apple move into Metal API? now you can't virtualize it in VirtualBox and VMware etc
spoco: look up wingsuit proximity flying, that's some real shit
Scyned: hi!!
Causevd: just cut / paste EZ
umps: have you seen devon crawford?
Thomasbrah: twitch spinoff PogChamp
Vyshnevskyi: @georgehotz like the guy who went for eagle's egg in Silicon Valley? Kappa
th3_maj0r: A lot of people died live on facebook while they do dangerous things
spoco: one dude livestreamed hitting a rock in a wingsuit to facebook, oops
DrRobotvinnik: dayum
nmuntz_: how would you like the docker image to work? not sure I understood what you wanted fixed
Draterini: there are people who commit suicide during the live stream and there are people paying to see that man its not a big deal
kanogger: svg gang
Causevd: TriHard
MichaelMcMillan: heyyyy george
toolegit2quit_: @spoco as he was dying, you could hear the bells of the cows since it was in a Swiss valley (cc: @georgehotz )
Dsplits: Is college worth it?
MichaelMcMillan: I broke out of the simulation today
NabZzz: i already saw 2 guys die in the middle of a soccer field live on tv
Causevd: no Dsplits
yeah_haey: please make some csgo HvH hacks or watch videos on youtube about watch aimware
kozgn: @georgehotz do you know the new zealand shooting?
MichaelMcMillan: Turns out you just need to take a massive dump
jamiryu06: lol
Biffingtonn: lmao
umps: what about the dude that took a shotgun to the dome on live tv
funwayz: Google chrome again?
NabZzz: there's TOS though LUL
adriaroms: ex startup CEO? what?
kanogger: no you're on twitch
myaocat: what do you think about apple move into Metal API? now you can't virtualize it in VirtualBox and VMware etc
NabZzz: well a guy streamed himself killing people with a go pro, looked like some fps gameplay
bdhrocks: bdhrocks subscribed at Tier 1.
Dsplits: how stressful was running a company?
andreccosta: Boeing has come out saying there's nothing wrong with the plane. The pilots just have the appropriate training and didn't know to turn the system off?!
andreccosta: *didn't
NabZzz: DarwinAwards.TV LUL
Causevd: u still in same house where comma is?
keepingtrckofthisacct: FailArmy x 2
andreccosta: Yeah, MCAS.
shutchie: !uptime
umps: what is your keyboard?
d3rmesaaa: Listen GEORGE you gotta be more active iv u wanna reach the mill on the gram bitchhhhhhhhhh
yeah_haey: when are you making a 3D engine
elitetech101: there was a way to turn it on
JonThomasK: How did that get past testing?
elitetech101: off*
Bombapil0t: build2fail
elitetech101: but they were not educated*
jkpfeffer: So short Boeing?
gazny: What about the DLC
Thomasbrah: man thats nutty
gunnaren: Yey - made it to a livestream! :D
umps: !keyboard
andreccosta: I believe you can override it but not turn it off. And apparently the pilots didn't know how to because no training? Something like that. Not sure.
Filiadelski: A toaster oven has better failsafes
Thomasbrah: i dont want to fly
adriaroms: Boeing has a DLC update for mcas
d3rmesaaa: kay whats gonna do today
tybutnowyoudie: LUL
revolutionist123: LUL
AnAnonymousCheerer: anon100
myaocat: what if you dont understand well the wikipedia BibleThump
BRrrh: why is it lagging every 5 seconds
andreccosta: LUL
d3rmesaaa: his old pc
JonThomasK: "do you want to die option"
verxile: I did not want to remember worst porn video I've ever seen :(
andreccosta: "Do you want the safety pack with your airplane sir?"
myaocat: @BRrrh because fps drops. i believe it's hardware and not connection
Causevd: the reason why stream is lagging is because the food is STILL coming
luhartt: shamaWayment
yeah_haey: whe nare you making a 3d engine
tornyl: you should buy better pc
andreas_bylund: Is this buffer-heaven?
yeah_haey: you should show some of your unreleased projects some day
myaocat: is this AMA? if yes, what do you think about snowden?
Draterini: What is the name of your keyboard btw?
andreccosta: I'm flying Ryanair next week. Don't jinx it. Kappa
Elnonono: can't see
alluxua: Whoops, I still have some Boeing stocks
bsx1123: airlinelist.co
kanogger: how about chinese airlines?
umps: UAE airlines super safe... ironig LUL
Causevd: u invested in bitcoin?
boy_milk: i've finally caught you live!
andreccosta: Like the Max 8 Kappa
KhrisDoes: Where would commaai be in that list for autonomous vehicles? @georgehotz
andreccosta: ("Safety pack" not included)
Meapzor: move the list to th right, you are covering it
Draterini: how about the turkish airlines?
d3rmesaaa: fuck bitcoin tho
radeon04: Do you think aliens built pyramids? :D
umps: what's your keyboard you use
gunnaren: how's instagram?
nmuntz_: how would you like the docker image to work? not sure I understood what you wanted fixed
dannyy_r: we love rant
un3okapi: when are we going to get spacex commercial rockets?
tybutnowyoudie: do you think formal methods could somehow be used to verify stuff in machine learning, like a neural network?
JonThomasK: sell sell sell
th3_maj0r: So... we live in a simulation?
bsx1123: whick broker?
iTeQo_: Bro buy $VNRX
Causevd: PogChamp
umps: what's super micro
pau1riddle: Martin Shkreli taught us that you shouldn't invest your own money, since you don't have enough
andreccosta: When the story about the "spying" microchip make out?
0TestUser: what about crypto ? Kappa
phillyspoon: Thoughts on 5G if you have any?
michael31415926535: morning afternoon evening George
myaocat: did you really give your autograph? i saw on ctf Blaze CTF 2016 that first prize is your autograph.. not sure if it's true... ps: im not that good at ctf
d3rmesaaa: id dont really know what to think of mr robot tbh
yeah_haey: show some of your unreleased projects
umps: but what about crypto
Draterini: WAIT! What is the name of your keyboard
andreccosta: At least there's a Kappa there to signal it.